<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>5850484116</g:id>
      <g:title>Egardenkart Bamboo FencingPlastic (Green)</g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour GreenBrand EgardenkartStyle GardenProduct dimensions 119L x 10W centimetersAbout this itemBamboo Fencing Plastic GreenBamboo Fencing Plastic GreenVersatile design Perfect for making an attractive screen or fence for your garden</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/99f8a958-2689-4221-a853-0f57d54901dd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e9f9c880-db53-4f63-928e-29af5f6a343b/web/1_1736397661233.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>27 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058504841162</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6395351334</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wooden Storage Box Organizer Antique Wooden Jewelry Box For Jewelry</g:title>
      <g:description>Orderly Storage: This wooden jewelry box can help you store your accessories, keep your desktop tidy, and protect your jewelry from loss or damage. Buckle Design: This small organizer box is designed with alloy buckle, which is convenient to open and closeNatural wood material and designed for most accessories storage needs. It can be used to protect your make-up and, jewelry or anything that you like. deal for self-use or for a gift purpose. Antique distressed jewelry box, with a strong retro feeling, simple and generous, placed on your makeup table, can also decorate your space, reflect your unique taste.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/960d889b-8cd4-4df1-bdec-1d20c0d1c2eb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d04e6de0-f644-4493-aef3-d1610db4b318/web/1_1736399402924.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>87.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063953513348</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9983128591</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Marble Umbrella Parasol Base For Outdoor Garden Patio Sunshade Umbrella Holder Stand </g:title>
      <g:description>Material: This umbrella base is made of strong granite and metal stand, it’s extremely stable and ensure your parasol stand still in windy days. Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Any parasol with a maximum pole diameter of 5cm can be used with this base. Knob Fixing: The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: It can be used at home, villas, hotels, terraces, balconies, resorts, water parks, barbecue bars, western restaurants, beauty salons, company rest area, etc.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/894c34f2-9a4b-463e-9634-be32d4f1ce38</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/52d9e95f-ce30-437a-8c3f-a4b14140eeab/web/1_1736398055538.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>125.82 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0099831285915</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9295628626</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Large Collapsible Wagon Cart Heavy Duty Wagon Garden Carts with 8" All Terrain Wheels</g:title>
      <g:description>frame supports 60 kg / 132 lb;Folding utility vehicles are ideal for transporting shopping, family outingsThe 360-degree beach wheels and the adjustable handle - the folding cart has heavy and thick rubber wheels - rotate 360,Convenient and compact storage - easy to fold and simple storage;Instant installation, no assembly required;It can be folded into a handbag for easy storage. Sturdy and washable -- the folding station wagon is made of 601D waterproof polyester, detachable and easy to clean by hand or hose. The camping beach station wagon frame is made of steel. The sturdy black steel frame of the beach outdoor multifunctional station wagon frame is more stable</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cc2b577b-c9d5-4ae7-a023-5c4883b17ed7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2392d8e4-12b4-43f8-961b-b8930d28e167/web/1_1736398248488.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>253 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092956286263</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5400750300</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wood Chairs and Table Bistro Set - Folding Outdoor Patio Dining Table</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Wood Chairs and Table Bistro Set - Folding Outdoor Patio Dining Table Set - 3 Pcs Metal Foldable Dining Table Set For Home Outdoor Balcony Terrace Use – Garden Furniture – Office FurnitureColour WhiteBrand Yatai DecorSize SmallItem weight 11. 02 PoundsAssembly required YesAbout this itemBrand: YataiIs assembly required: TrueItem shape: RectangularRoom type: Patio Garden</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8fd2488f-d32a-4dc7-87aa-94b8242723b9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ec2170d1-589e-4cc1-8352-26482f976ccf/web/1_1736400399912.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>229.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054007503002</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8947672249</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Outdoor Sun Shade Cover Deck Window Door Canopy Shelter Foldable Awning</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Outdoor Sun Shade Cover Deck Window Door Canopy Shelter Foldable Awning with Manual Crank Handle Retractable Patio Awning, UV and Water-Resistant, Aluminum Awnings (Cream)Dimensions: This 400x250 cm patio retractable sun shade is ideal for shading of windows and balcony door, making your house look elegantMaterial: The retractable awning is made of high quality polyester and PU coating fabric, which is water resistant, anti ultraviolet, resistant to sun fading the rust-resistant metal frame is sturdy for long term use. Adjustable: This manually retractable awning features a long hand crank that opens and closes the awning smoothly and quietly. It's easily adjustable to meet your sun or shade needs. Low Heat: Protect your exterior from the sun' damaging UV rays and effectively reduce the heat inside your home all while possibly lowering your cooling bill. Easy install: Our sturdy retractable sunshade awning with an aluminum frame can easily attach to a plain cement wall or stable unrendered brickwork with matching screws.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/299fc74e-8c33-4e98-9dd8-4bcafa0f54f5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/11c09406-bb1f-4ea0-8eff-f5aa3434798a/web/1_1736400183950.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>999 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089476722494</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9804492273</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Solid Umbrella Parasol Base For Outdoor Garden Patio</g:title>
      <g:description>Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. Material: This umbrella stand is made of strong plastic. It is waterproof, heat-resistant, wear-resistant with strong UV resistance and permanent corrosion. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Any parasol with a maximum pole diameter of 4cm can be used with this base. Knob Fixing: The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: It can be used at home, villas, hotels, terraces, balconies, resorts, water parks, barbecue bars, western restaurants, beauty salons, company rest area, etc.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/083be05e-4ec3-4898-bf7e-55e49b873f86</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/747a8929-8816-4a91-b851-3e0f6caf6b78/web/1_1736405786624.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>72.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098044922730</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9499325233</g:id>
      <g:title>Home-Complete Walk-in Greenhouse- Indoor Outdoor with 8 Sturdy Shelves</g:title>
      <g:description>8-SHELF GREENHOUSE KIT - The 8 greenhouse shelves provide plenty of room for trays, pots, or planters of anything you want to grow. Each shelf comes with zip ties to secure them to the sturdy metal frame, preventing them from tipping over. INDOOR OR OUTDOOR - This portable greenhouse is ideal for both indoor and outdoor use in your backyard, courtyard, patio, deck, or in the basement or garage. The clear PVC cover helps protect seedlings from frost or pests for an ideal growing environment. EASY ASSEMBLY - With no tools required, the green houses for outside are simple to assemble. Simply follow the included instructions and connect the rods of this outdoor greenhouse and use the included stakes and guy lines for added stability. VERSATILE USE - This outdoor or indoor greenhouse is a perfect way to extend your growing season for various herbs, vegetables, and fruit-bearing plants, as well as for showcasing beautiful perennials or holding gardening supplies in the offseason. PRODUCT DETAILS - Materials: Steel Frame and PVC Cover. Dimensions: (L) 56. 3” x (W) 56. 3” x (H) 76. 7”. Includes: Stakes, Guy Lines, and Zip Ties. Color: Green with Clear Cover.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/adc56f61-2daf-4ea0-bc78-a693592e0cc3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ab64d16a-e0e6-45c7-87e2-aa73b762c62e/web/1_1736399575826.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>244.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094993252331</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1453050007</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wooden Storage Box Organizer Antique Wooden Jewelry Box</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemName: Antique Wooden Jewelry BoxSize: L-40cm, H-16cm, W-27cmNatural wood material and designed for most accessories storage needs. It can be used to protect your make-up and, jewelry or anything that you like. deal for self-use or for a gift purpose. Note: Flowers are not included.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d1cbbd47-367c-44ab-bd3c-1dfbba595cd6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e4dd883d-467e-4442-8e66-852432660b44/web/1_1736402898857.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014530500077</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3539268146</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Outdoor Sun Shade Cover Deck Window Door Canopy Shelter Foldable Awning with Manual </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: This 300x200 cm patio retractable sun shade is ideal for shading of windows and balcony door, making your house look elegantMaterial: The retractable awning is made of high quality polyester and PU coating fabric, which is water resistant, anti ultraviolet, resistant to sun fading the rust-resistant metal frame is sturdy for long term use. Adjustable: This manually retractable awning features a long hand crank that opens and closes the awning smoothly and quietly. It's easily adjustable to meet your sun or shade needs. Low Heat: Protect your exterior from the sun' damaging UV rays and effectively reduce the heat inside your home all while possibly lowering your cooling bill. Easy install: Our sturdy retractable sunshade awning with an aluminum frame can easily attach to a plain cement wall or stable unrendered brickwork with matching screws.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7413d9b1-2eaa-458a-80d6-6ae9292cda2c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2b058c35-6062-449c-8386-ca79824e32a1/web/2_1736408740069.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>788 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035392681469</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8226472266</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Set of 4 Folding Chairs With Folding Table - Lightweight Outdoor Camping Chair Table Set</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimension: Chair Size: Length - 34cm, Width – 37cm, Height – 37cm, Table Size: Length -47cm, Width – 47cm, Height – 40cm. Durability: The chairs and table are constructed from high quality materials that are designed to withstand the weather and whatever else you may throw at them. They can hold up to 120KG, so these chairs are more than capable of supporting most people. Versatility: Ideal for hunting, motorcycling, fishing, mountaineering, beach, BBQ, road trip, tailgate party, sport events and anyone looking for light travel without the bulk. These YATAI camping chairs are the ideal way to soak up the summer sun when the weather gets warmer. Featuring a handy drink holder in the table these chairs and table set is ideal for sitting back and relaxing. Easy To Clean: This folding chair table set is great not only for outdoor activities such as mountain climbing, fishing, caps, BBQ, but also indoors. When it gets dirty, all you have to do is wipe the metal pole, and the fabric can be washed by hand like normal clothes. Easy to carry: Weighing just 500g per chair, these camping chairs will have no problems being transported or stored away. A carrier bag is also included with this product, which can be folded away in seconds, to make moving these chairs even easier. They are easy to move around your garden so you will be able to position yourself in the prime sunny spots.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/564212a8-4811-4468-9d47-4a5c919f5ef7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1a328f2f-c3f2-4534-aeef-71cf4cd5c431/web/1_1736404360351.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>124.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082264722669</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5132465848</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Artificial Money Plant 1.7 Meter High Artificial Tree in Plastic </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height – 170cm, Diameter – 75cm, Pot Size: Height – 13cm, Diameter – 15cm. High-Quality Material: Nearly natural PVC plastic branches, and plastic pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a4173333-309e-4a4e-b676-cacc41850018</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a79f8bf2-9448-4fcb-9b25-f16580801a30/web/4_1736400588227.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>143.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051324658484</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3878736415</g:id>
      <g:title>Egardenkart Artificial Grass Carpet 26mm Fake Grass Turf 2meters </g:title>
      <g:description>Size: 200cm x 100cmColor: GreenBrand EgardenkartMaterial features NaturalColour GreenSpecial features Air PurificationExpected blooming period Year RoundAbout this itemBrand: Egardenkart26mm Pile Height. Appearance and texture of real grass. Soft, non-abrasive, non-absorbent fiber.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d27cca3-5ad3-4aae-b2e2-d9a310a1fbe2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ad64a0d-dd69-4b0c-9cf9-17d025ba866a/web/1_1736402245782.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>52.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038787364152</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1177420075</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Rectangular Umbrella UV Protection With Plastic Base Water Sand Filled Waterproof</g:title>
      <g:description>Overall Dimension: Length - 285cm, Width - 196cm, Height – 255cm. Base Size: Height – 40cm, Diameters – 50cm. Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol Umbrella with base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. High-Quality Material: Umbrella is made with high-quality waterproof, UV protection and fade-resistant fabric, aid in preventing sun-induced skin damage, to last for years of enjoyment. Parasol base is made of plastic and can be filled with water or sand to increase the weight to improve the stability of the umbrella under windy conditions. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: Designed to provide shade from sun &amp;amp; protection from rain while you spend your time outdoors. Ideal for your garden, backyard or patio setting. When not in use or in inclement weather, we advise storing the parasol in a cool and dry indoor place.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ef47f51f-9caa-4627-9be6-f944d40e5079</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8a086b0a-b71e-4a46-ab67-6b2015822a32/web/1_1736419249443.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>299 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011774200756</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5897237077</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Expandable Wooden Fence Climbing Plants Flower Bed Edging Wooden Panels For Partition</g:title>
      <g:description>Material: Solid wood, environmental protection, moisture-proof and anti-UV. Approximate Size: Fully Expanded- Height – 120cm, Length – 130cm. It can be expanded and folded to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. Design: Beautiful simple style appearance, high quality, lightweight, sturdy and durability for last for years. YATAI portable wooden fence can be used as garden fence, partition wall as an ivy, vine, roses and other climbing plants growing aid of various. Versatile Uses: Perfect for gardens, landscaping, flowerbeds, courtyard, paths, border and lawns, or flower planting. The wooden panel fits any contour for custom landscaping, around trees, flower beds, bushes, garden, yard, and more can be used to decorate your outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ebd9472f-8955-471a-a163-45a6d0853443</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e2bc2e70-cf59-4c15-9d7f-94e523b68727/web/1_1736404726935.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>166.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058972370775</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8393380219</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Large Collapsible Wagon Cart Heavy Duty Wagon Garden Carts</g:title>
      <g:description>Product dimensions 95D x 57W x 106H centimetersBrand Yatai DecorMaterial Polyester, Alloy Steel, RubberSpecial features Waterproof, Sturdy, CollapsibleNumber of shelves 1About this itemLarge capacity, large internal size 95 x 57 x 106 cm Sturdy frame supports 60 kg / 132 lb;Folding utility vehicles are ideal for transporting shopping, family outingsThe 360-degree beach wheels and the adjustable handle - the folding cart has heavy and thick rubber wheels - rotate 360,Convenient and compact storage - easy to fold and simple storage;Instant installation, no assembly required;It can be folded into a handbag for easy storage. Sturdy and washable -- the folding station wagon is made of 601D waterproof polyester, detachable and easy to clean by hand or hose. The camping beach station wagon frame is made of steel. The sturdy black steel frame of the beach outdoor</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d32691c-1810-4605-8429-c9ddf9907241</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7e5fef74-8f54-4441-9d1a-dcee5fe6bc12/web/1_1736401176051.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>289.08 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083933802194</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3750663523</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Set of 2 Concrete Vase, Cylinder Shape Modern Plant Pot with Drainage Hole</g:title>
      <g:description>🌟 Stylish and Functional: With its modern design and practical features, our concrete vase combines style and functionality, making it a must-have accessory for any decor enthusiast. 💐 Modern Cylinder Design: Elevate your decor with our sleek and stylish concrete vase, featuring a contemporary cylinder shape that adds a modern touch to any space. 🎨 Customizable Decor: Personalize your space with our concrete vase, allowing you to showcase your favorite plants and flowers while complementing your existing decor style. 🌿 Sturdy Textured Construction: Crafted from durable concrete with a stylish textured design, our vase ensures long-lasting quality and adds visual interest to any room or outdoor area. 🌼 Room Enhancement: Add a touch of nature to any room with our floor vase, serving as a striking decor piece that enhances the ambiance and visual appeal of your home or office. 🌸 Perfect for Flower Arrangements: Create stunning floral displays and centerpieces with our vase, perfect for weddings, parties, and special events, adding charm and beauty to any occasion. 🏡 Ideal for Home and Office: Whether placed in the living room, office, or event venue, our floor vase adds a touch of sophistication and elegance to any setting.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8d78e193-6ab1-47fd-a17b-37c7c1d72278</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/503f1bf4-3042-4f87-83be-0d20d8a8d5fb/web/1_1736403905839.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>260 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037506635238</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1391835133</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Premium Artificial Bamboo Tree, 210cm Sturdy  Tall Artificial Plants with Pots</g:title>
      <g:description>🌿Sturdy &amp;amp; Tall: Standing at an impressive 210cm, this artificial bamboo tree adds a touch of elegance and height to any space, indoors or outdoors. ☀️ UV Resistant: Crafted with UV-resistant materials, this artificial plant is built to withstand sunlight exposure without fading, making it perfect for both indoor and outdoor use. 🌱 No Maintenance: Enjoy the beauty of lush green bamboo leaves without the hassle of watering or pruning. This fake plant requires no maintenance, allowing you to enjoy its lifelike appearance hassle-free. 🌿 Versatile Usage: Ideal for home office decor, living rooms, bedrooms, and more, this artificial bamboo tree complements a wide range of decor styles, adding a touch of tranquility to any space. 🌿 Lifelike Green Leaves: The realistic design of the bamboo leaves adds a natural touch to any setting, creating a serene and inviting atmosphere. 🌱 Low-Maintenance: Say goodbye to watering and pruning! This artificial bamboo tree stays lush and green year-round with minimal upkeep, making it an ideal choice for busy lifestyles. 🏡 Indoor/Outdoor Decor: Enhance the ambiance of your home or office with this versatile artificial bamboo tree. Whether placed indoors as a statement piece or outdoors to add greenery to your garden or patio, it exudes timeless charm.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7baca890-1be4-4ead-abc8-cfd65ae57a32</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0ebad16a-9159-47c1-8d20-22697c51e3b2/web/1_1736406126747.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>197.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013918351331</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8792393957</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor YATAI Solid Metal Umbrella Parasol Base For Outdoor Garden Patio</g:title>
      <g:description>Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. Material: This umbrella stand is made of strong plastic. It is waterproof, heat-resistant, wear-resistant with strong UV resistance and permanent corrosion. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Any parasol with a maximum pole diameter of 4cm can be used with this base. Knob Fixing: The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: It can be used at home, villas, hotels, terraces, balconies, resorts, water parks, barbecue bars, western restaurants, beauty salons, company rest area, etc.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aa398ad5-f9de-4aaa-bb80-9970207bb290</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/11de7259-01c5-4e12-9cff-ce0fdcd81578/web/3_1736405983943.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>88.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0087923939570</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1433008200</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor 22 Cm Diameter Garden Plant Support, Plant Cage Support</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemDimensions:- Height:- 140cm (Adjustable) , Diameter:- 22CmOur Plant Cages and Supports with powder coating surface treatment, gives a better anti-rust ability. Durable, and suitable for all kinds of weather. The smooth surface is easy to clean for daily maintenance. It is very suitable for maximizing the limited gardening space. It is easy to fix in the soil. This garden cage is specially designed for the vertical climbing of plants with vegetable or tomato support, better through the plant circulation and the natural ripening of the fruits. No need for any tools, one person can complete the assembly by hand. These garden arch trellis help keep ties in place, are also sealed at the tips to ensure they are easy to drive into most garden soils or flowers pot.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d9306ea9-2e32-4337-903e-616fe9763a2e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2683dd08-c422-4b55-989c-3e298b4538c2/web/1_1736405668944.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>80.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014330082001</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1506603344</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 30mm Artificial Grass Carpet Fake Grass Mat - Realistic  Thick Turf Lawn Rug Carpet -Indoor</g:title>
      <g:description>MATERIAL: It is made of super-strong high-density polyethylene that's soft and lush, UV-proof, weather resistant, low-maintenance, providing you with year-round green and turf enjoyment. MULTI PURPOSE USE: You can put it in your balcony, dining room, backyard, terrace, swimming pools, patio, or make your own golf putting green and baseball playground. INDOOR/OUTDOOR: This grass carpet is designed for both indoor and outdoor use. Place it in the entryway of your home, living room, bathroom or kitchen. Also used as mat, carpet in indoor. ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY: It is soft and comfortable, no irritating odor. You can step on barefoot; it does not hurt your feet. EASY INSTALLATION/ CUSTOMIZED SIZE: We can customize any size that you need for you! YATAI Artificial Grass Carpet comes in a roll which is ready made in the size marked above. You only need to choose an area to put and roll out the grass and you are done! You can even cut the grass roll into your sizes to better accommodate your place. It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5c0ee10e-d941-4428-b85e-dfafe2152cf3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/260d393d-7add-442a-a5ef-a73829e74241/web/1_1736405280129.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>467.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015066033442</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2603626543</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Concrete Vase with Drainage Hole, Circular Design Planters</g:title>
      <g:description>Size: Height-43cm, Diameter-32cm. (Plant is not included). 💐 Chic Matte Black Concrete Vase: Elevate your floral arrangements with our chic matte black concrete vase, adding a touch of sophistication to any space. 🌿 Circular Design Planters: Our circular design planters offer a sleek and modern aesthetic, perfect for showcasing indoor plants and enhancing your home decor. 🍃Durable &amp;amp; Versatile: Crafted from durable concrete, our vase with drainage hole is versatile enough to be used both indoors and outdoors, adding style to your patio, garden, or office. 🍃 Drainage Hole Included: Ensure proper drainage for your plants with the built-in drainage hole, promoting healthy growth and preventing waterlogging. 🌟 Garden Accessories: Enhance your garden decor with our concrete pots, adding a touch of elegance and sophistication to your outdoor oasis. 🏡 Home Office Patio Garden Decor: Whether adorning your home, office, patio, or garden, our concrete vase serves as a versatile decor piece, blending seamlessly with any environment.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cd5e4e3b-d77c-4f1c-9d7c-35336e93a40c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f1791b5-cae3-49d7-bd4e-6037d962ae3c/web/1_1736406633734.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>99 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026036265435</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3486640104</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Heavy Duty Parasol Plastic Base For Umbrella Patio Sunshade Umbrella Stand</g:title>
      <g:description>Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. Material: This umbrella stand is made of strong and durable plastic. It is waterproof, heat-resistant, wear-resistant with strong UV resistance and permanent corrosion. Stability: Plastic parasol umbrella base can be filled with water or sand to increase the weight to improve the stability of the umbrella under windy conditions. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Any parasol with a maximum pole diameter of 4cm can be used with this base. Knob Fixing: The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: It can be used at home, villas, hotels, terraces, balconies, resorts, water parks, barbecue bars, western restaurants, beauty salons, company rest area, etc.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/77e14779-8ad3-4900-a034-181ba40d66b0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5c930249-7428-48b4-af83-a7c8783757b3/web/1_1736406819143.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>55.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0034866401046</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5049299211</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Premium Wooden Outdoor Bench – Durable 2-3 Seater Garden Furniture, 145cm</g:title>
      <g:description>Spacious and Comfortable Design: With dimensions of 145cm (W) x 55cm (D) x 88cm (H), this wooden bench comfortably accommodates 2 to 3 people. The ergonomic seat depth of 47cm ensures maximum relaxation. Durable Acacia Hardwood Construction: Crafted from premium acacia hardwood, known for its strength and resilience, this bench is built to last. Its natural wood finish adds elegance to any outdoor or indoor setting. Design: Elegant harmony bench with a natural straight grain look and rich golden-brown color, this bench is an elegant addition to your outdoor space. It comfortably seats 3 people and features comfortable armrests at either side. Its ability to naturally resist termites and other insects, rot, decay and moisture ensure that it will last long and will keep its looks despite regular use. Easy Assembly: Comes with pre-drilled holes and clear instructions for hassle-free assembly in just minutes. Versatile Use: Ideal for gardens, patios, balconies, living rooms, and commercial spaces like cafes and hotels. Its minimalist design complements various decor styles.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/355ddd7d-274b-4c2a-aefd-b2569a1ea741</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/17140793-aaa4-4e2e-987f-ff05d7757d5f/web/1_1736407210091.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050492992116</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6960195298</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Standing Rustic Wooden Tall Fence Trellis Spaced Picket Fence Garden Creations Patio</g:title>
      <g:description>Material WoodColour GreyBrand Yatai DecorStyle RusticAssembly required YesAbout this itemDimensions: Approx. Length - 90cm, Height - 184cmHigh-Quality Material: Made with High quality pure solid wood maintenance-free weather resistant Eco-friendly. It comes with a wooden stand. The wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front yard and garden area decoration or any other place. Assembles and installs with relative ease- little to no digging required compared to a normal one. Simply insert included pointed stakes into the ground or use a cordless drill and auger bit in hard groundYATAI fences are excellent as a divider and climbing nail support. Use them as fences, divider, pedestrian, walkway fence, or trellis. These fences are extremely durable, so count on them to enhance your garden for many years to come.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d3bd7253-354d-4e5c-aea2-9250de247bfb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/59a7cd7b-68ba-448a-b325-a299e0fa153f/web/1_1736407020916.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>224.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069601952989</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1052074927</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wood Chair and Table For your Perfect Home – Metal Folding Dining Table Set</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour multiBrand Yatai DecorSize SmallStyle Easy To Clean, Durable, Relaxing, Strong, RelaxedAssembly required YesAbout this itemChair Size: Height - 78cm, Width - 48cm, Length-42cm. Table Size: Height - 71cm, Diameters - 55cm. Table folds down for easy storage. Material: Made of hardy wood and metal, its strong and durable. This 3pc bistro set including one square table and two folding chairs. The suitable size prefers for patio, garden, bistro, balcony or room. The high chair back gives you good support and makes you more relaxed. This set is made with wood and metal frame!it's perfect for placing on your patio. balconies and smaller gardens. Best of all, each piece offers a folded design for convenient storage in the offseason. This bistro set with table and 2 chairs set is ideal for relaxing or entertaining in the sunshine. The small, round table is made from hardwood and folds for easy storage. The 2 folding chairs fit comfortably around the table and can be stowed easily.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e75bd2fe-d9d8-4ee7-88ba-c24ae78731a2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4ae5b40c-4a21-4326-bec9-805c2e3fcd1c/web/1_1736407381879.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>215.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010520749273</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2211000297</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Outdoor Essentials Outdoor Faux Rock - for Landscaping, Yard Décor,  Gardens</g:title>
      <g:description>Material ResinBrand Yatai DecorColour GreyShape IrregularNumber of Items 1About this itemDimensions:- Length-21cm, Width- 12cm, Height-30cmMaterial:- Made of durable Polyresin construction, Hand Painted Natural Stone Color is with rust, weather and UV resistant to keep your rock looking new overtime. Artificial rocks can be used to create visually appealing landscapes without the need for natural stones. They come in a variety of shapes, sizes, and colors, allowing for customization and versatility in landscaping design. They are weather-resistant and durable, designed to withstand outdoor elements such as rain, UV rays, and temperature fluctuations. They can be used in both residential and commercial landscaping projects, enhancing the beauty of gardens, parks, golf courses, and more.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a3314536-02eb-47f3-8a5f-e0a7fdb450d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d6530af0-ca4f-4fa6-806d-ed5c9f2ddc02/web/1_1736407818303.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>71.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022110002972</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9598415307</g:id>
      <g:title>Artificial Green Grass Carpet, Garden Grass, Grass Carpet, Green Carpet</g:title>
      <g:description>Indoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorSpecial features Eco FriendlyExpected blooming period Year RoundItem weight 5 KilogramsSunlight exposure Full SunAbout this itemBrand: YATAIMaterial: PlasticSize: 30mm, 2 square meters (200x100cm)Features: It gives a natural appearance and is green all year round. It is UV stabilized. 100% recyclable. Regular anti-compaction pellet shape. It is safe and clean. Does not release dust or bad odor. It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/954706de-9955-4467-8326-04057365a9df</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4aef4a93-dadb-44e8-9063-83ef78c1b124/web/1_1736407534375.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>92 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095984153071</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1362353000</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Mini Folding Aluminium Table Folding Table Portable</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand Yatai DecorProduct dimensions 29D x 29W x 12H centimetersItem weight 1 KilogramsFrame material WoodColour SilverAbout this itemBrand: Yatai DecorItem shape: RectangularTop Material: Pine WoodIs assembly required: False</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/135ff0b7-362b-41f2-a266-f192bb0e5412</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c2d98a78-435c-4e73-9484-b4ae34b7f52f/web/1_1736408235623.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>86.90 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0013623530007</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8560867341</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Pack of 10 Wooden Tiles, Hardwood Decking Tiles with Snap  Plastic Base</g:title>
      <g:description>🌳 Premium Hardwood Tiles: Pack of 10 wooden tiles for durable and anti-slip decking, perfect for outdoor and indoor spaces. 🏡 Easy Installation: Interlocking design with snap &amp;amp; plastic base for hassle-free installation, ideal for DIY enthusiasts. 🌞 Versatile Use: Transform your patio, garden, balcony, or backyard with these decorative deck tiles. 🏊‍♂️ Poolside Charm: Enhance your swimming pool area with these stylish and practical wooden floor tiles. 🌿 Natural Beauty: Enjoy the warmth and elegance of timber decking tiles, perfect for creating inviting outdoor spaces. 🌼 Balcony Decor: Elevate your balcony decor with these interlocking deck tiles, adding charm and functionality. 🛠️ DIY Friendly: Easily create your terrace or wooden patio with this convenient decking tile set. 🏖️ Relaxing Retreat: Create a serene outdoor oasis with these exterior deck tiles, perfect for relaxation and entertainment. 🌟 Quality Assurance: Made from premium hardwood for long-lasting durability and aesthetic appeal. 🍃 Environmentally Friendly: Sustainable wooden interlocking tiles for eco-conscious outdoor living spaces.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c2f40349-9971-4616-a398-6bc028a5afb2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/03223474-6a99-4943-b1e5-8d5db6970eed/web/1_1736410528501.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>118 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085608673412</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3251470031</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Artificial Plant with Pot, Lifelike Pincushion Peperomia Flower Arrangements</g:title>
      <g:description>🌿 Lifelike Flower Arrangements: Add a touch of nature to your space with our lifelike artificial plant, featuring vibrant green leaves and realistic details. 🌸 Artificial Flowers for Decoration: Incorporate these artificial plants into your decor, offering versatility and long-lasting beauty for various decorative purposes. 🌿 Artificial Plant with Pot: Each arrangement comes with a sleek white pot, providing a stylish and ready-to-display solution for effortless decorating. 🏡 No-Maintenance Indoor Plants: Enjoy the beauty of plants without the hassle of upkeep, as our artificial flower arrangements require no watering or pruning. 🌱 UV Resistant: Crafted with UV-resistant materials, these artificial plants are suitable for indoor use, maintaining their vibrant color even in sunlight. 🌼 Versatile Decor: Elevate your home, office, or event decor with these sleek and modern artificial plants, perfect for adding a fresh and contemporary look. 🌿 Office Decor: Enhance your workspace with these no-maintenance indoor plants, bringing a sense of tranquility and freshness to your office environment.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/496f9329-8ce5-4aa3-8cbc-8f9c6fbf3c3b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4c83e60e-960d-4cc5-be9a-7dbb67fe8653/web/1_1736408039228.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032514700312</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5511296098</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor Plastic Pots For Plants Vase Big Plants </g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour WhiteSpecial features LightweightStyle GardenPlanter form Plant PotAbout this itemBrand: Yatai DecorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: Round</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8586a161-9bce-4992-953e-81e52b9ee80a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/622e6b24-5cf9-4ced-a915-312a55caf09b/web/1_1736408584119.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>38.61 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055112960988</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9578109818</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor Plastic Pots For Plants Vase Big Plants </g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour BlueSpecial features Outdoor SuitabilityStyle GardenPlanter form Plant PotAbout this itemBrand: Yatai DecorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: Round</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/62ff41d9-c309-46ce-921c-d636ff2dd56f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5d5fe089-cd25-4f12-b2fb-77aaded8aac7/web/1_1736408394123.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>38.61 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095781098186</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3880063346</g:id>
      <g:title>artificial Plants 1.6 Meters alocasia Tree Plant, artificial Tree, Garden Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>Name: Artificial Alocasia TreeMaterial: Feel over glue leavesSize: About 1. 6 meters highFeatures: It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. Made from high-quality materials and vibrant colors.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/add33013-a55b-4b2f-95f0-db3850cc8dbc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6fdc2107-a302-47fa-a89b-542fa1a1b6f4/web/1_1736408874445.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038800633463</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7468832922</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Pack of 2 Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor Plastic Pots For Plants Vase</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand: Yatai decorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: RoundFinish type: PolishedBrand: Yatai DecorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopYatai Decor Pack of 2 Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor Plastic Pots For Plants Vase Big Plants Plant Pots For Indoor Garden Pots Vegetable Planter Box Outdoor Plants (White)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9908175a-619a-4340-8863-c809573251aa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0133c149-903d-425a-b529-8557bddc0f5c/web/1_1736409051373.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>68.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074688329227</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3132245280</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Round Umbrella UV Protection With Plastic Base Waterproof</g:title>
      <g:description>Overall Dimension: Total Height – 220cm, Diameters –200cm, Base Size: Height – 44cm, Diameters – 44cm. Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol Umbrella with base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. High-Quality Material: Umbrella is made with high-quality waterproof, UV protection and fade-resistant fabric, aid in preventing sun-induced skin damage, to last for years of enjoyment. Parasol base is made of plastic and can be filled with water or sand to increase the weight to improve the stability of the umbrella under windy conditions. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. The base comes with a manual tightening knob, used to fix the umbrella to the base to support the umbrella. Usage: Designed to provide shade from sun &amp;amp; protection from rain while you spend your time outdoors. Ideal for your garden, backyard or patio setting. When not in use or in inclement weather, we advise storing the parasol in a cool and dry indoor place.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/15608c3a-019c-46a6-b91d-520c270dacbf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/23c1a3fe-c4bb-4b5d-be3a-60b6a3c89fc3/web/1_1736409326633.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>349 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0031322452802</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9022854085</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Pack of 2 Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor Plastic Pots For Plants Vase</g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour CoffeeSpecial features LightweightStyle ModernPlanter form Plant PotAbout this itemBrand: Yatai DecorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: Tabletop</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/07645215-3850-4d8a-ae73-99d46d04ef12</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e2ed50f6-372e-4380-a3f9-f4ab5f4062c2/web/1_1736409475603.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>60.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090228540853</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7133650277</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI  Artificial Grass  Mat - Realistic  Thick Turf Lawn Rug Carpet -Indoor Outdoor Garden Carpet </g:title>
      <g:description>MATERIAL: It is made of super-strong high-density polyethylene that's soft and lush, UV-proof, weather resistant, low-maintenance, providing you with year-round green and turf enjoyment. MULTI PURPOSE USE: You can put it in your balcony, dining room, backyard, terrace, swimming pools, patio, or make your own golf putting green and baseball playground. INDOOR/OUTDOOR: This grass carpet is designed for both indoor and outdoor use. Place it in the entryway of your home, living room, bathroom or kitchen. Also used as mat, carpet in indoor. ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY: It is soft and comfortable, no irritating odor. You can step on barefoot; it does not hurt your feet. EASY INSTALLATION/ CUSTOMIZED SIZE: We can customize any size that you need for you! YATAI Artificial Grass Carpet comes in a roll which is ready made in the size marked above. You only need to choose an area to put and roll out the grass and you are done! You can even cut the grass roll into your sizes to better accommodate your place. It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e3a4e93d-2979-4e2f-9a9b-ab67673dc4ab</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e608efcc-a426-4377-9005-50879c3a8f0e/web/1_1736409643276.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>661 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0071336502773</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1494878895</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Cactus Plant Cacti Fake Plant with Plastic Pot for Home Indoor/Outdoor Decoration </g:title>
      <g:description>Size: Height-175cm, Length-37cm, Pot Size: Height-14cm, Diameters-17cm Material: Nearly Natural (PVC Plastic), Plastic PotFeatures &amp;amp; Uses Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customersArtificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7c37e81f-14bc-4609-81cb-1bedf086434e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b92eaef6-7c3a-4572-91ae-52e82f2e75f0/web/1_1736411418499.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>450 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0014948788951</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7473997624</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 40mm Artificial Grass Carpet - Indoor Outdoor Garden Lawn Landscape Synthetic Grass Mat </g:title>
      <g:description>MATERIAL: It is made of super-strong high-density polyethylene that's soft and lush, UV-proof, weather resistant, low-maintenance, providing you with year-round green and turf enjoyment. MULTI PURPOSE USE: You can put it in your balcony, dining room, backyard, terrace, swimming pools, patio, or make your own golf putting green and baseball playground. INDOOR/OUTDOOR: This grass carpet is designed for both indoor and outdoor use. Place it in the entryway of your home, living room, bathroom or kitchen. Also used as mat, carpet in indoor. ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY: It is soft and comfortable, no irritating odor. You can step on barefoot; it does not hurt your feet. EASY INSTALLATION/ CUSTOMIZED SIZE: We can customize any size that you need for you! YATAI Artificial Grass Carpet comes in a roll which is ready made in the size marked above. You only need to choose an area to put and roll out the grass and you are done! You can even cut the grass roll into your sizes to better accommodate your place. It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1f52fcb8-9459-4e75-bdcb-a689e8c2fafd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ab6dad7-37e1-4ee7-9975-de777b142aa9/web/1_1736411239680.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>700 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074739976240</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4718100287</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Pop Up Gazebo Tent Canopy 2x2 Meters With 4 Legs Outdoor Garden Marquee</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Pop Up Gazebo Tent Canopy 2x2 Meters With 4 Legs Outdoor Garden Marquee with Water-resistant Cover – Folding Party Camping Tent – Frame &amp;amp; Canopy Tent Easy AssemblyDimensions: The gazebo measures Length – 200cm, Width – 200cm, with a max roof height of 310cm. Material: Made from a sturdy steel frame with a water-resistant khaki cover, the gazebo offers a great space for entertaining and protection from unsettled weather. Each leg is fully adjustable so you can stand the gazebo safely on uneven ground. Uses: Great for parties and outdoor dining, this easy to assemble pop up gazebo. The elegant canopy looks great and feels soft to the touch, helping to create a luxurious finish. This particular 2x2 meters model is a frame with canopy only and no sidewalls. This YATAI’s tent is simple yet effortless in style and is perfect for parties, BBQs, picnics, and lots of other personal outdoor celebrations. Assembly: Easy to assemble – the gazebo can be erected, anchored and taken down in minutes.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5afd8f70-e0f6-4e87-a971-6fb7672fde3c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a0da68f8-3485-41db-a5f3-920300ae490e/web/1_1736410827162.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>252 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0047181002874</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8016088377</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Solid Acacia Wood Sun Lounger Outdoor - Weather-Resistant Adjustable Recliner Patio Chairs </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height - 60 cm, Width - 55 cm, Length- 198 cm, (comfortably seats with cushions. Naturally resists termites, rot, decay &amp;amp; moisture. Strong &amp;amp; Durable: Made of hardy Acacia wood, oil finishing, strong and durable. Cushions made of 100% polyester fabric. Built To Last: Built with weather elements in mind, our sturdy wood construction is made of weather-resistant wood and durable canvas. Timeless Gift: Surprise somebody with this awesome outdoor furniture piece! The outdoor chaise is perfect for enjoying the summer weather. Comfortable: Our sun loungers are ergonomic and made of skin-friendly fabrics. The adjustable backrest allows you to choose from 5 levels of personalized comfort, you can lay down on your stomach to enjoy sunbath. Perfect For Outdoors: This relaxing chair is perfect for patios, decks, lawns, poolside and outdoors for enjoying sunshine, having a rest, chatting with your friends or holding party. Assembly Instructions Included: Packaged with detailed, step-by-step assembly instructions.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/38ebbb83-4e64-4c5f-bf80-eb476d530dbf</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f709146c-d6d7-40a0-b79f-a43af89f9145/web/1_1736409769778.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>412.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080160883774</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4032931689</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Luxurious Artificial Bonsai Tree Lifelike Artificial Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Luxurious Artificial Bonsai Tree Lifelike Artificial Plants with Pots,Enhance Your Living Space with Evergreen,Eco-Friendly, Maintenance Free Fake Plants for Home Office Decor (70 Cm)🌳 Lifelike Evergreen Elegance: Elevate your living space with the timeless beauty of this artificial bonsai tree, designed to enhance any room with its lifelike appearance. 🏡 Enhance Your Decor: Add a touch of greenery to your home or office decor with this luxurious artificial plant, bringing the beauty of nature indoors without the need for maintenance. ♻️ Eco-Friendly &amp;amp; Maintenance-Free: Enjoy the benefits of greenery without the hassle of watering or upkeep. This eco-friendly artificial bonsai tree requires no maintenance, offering long-lasting beauty. 🌿 Realistic Design: Crafted with attention to detail, this artificial plant features realistic green leaves and a natural-looking trunk, creating an authentic bonsai tree appearance. 🌱 Versatile Decor Accent: Perfect for any room in your home or office, this artificial bonsai tree adds a touch of sophistication to tabletops, shelves, or desks, enhancing your decor effortlessly. 🍃 High-Quality Materials: Made from high-quality materials, this artificial plant is built to last, ensuring years of enjoyment and beauty in your home or office decor. 🏢 Office Oasis: Create a calming oasis in your workspace with this maintenance-free artificial plant, providing a refreshing touch of greenery to your desk or office environment.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8ea9c576-1b7b-4208-9046-dac5bb89c4cc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/14f8447e-9a37-4b0e-8366-691ed682701e/web/2_1736411760063.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>175.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040329316895</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9487226294</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor – Plastic Pots For Plants Vase</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Plastic Plant Pot For Indoor – Plastic Pots For Plants Vase Succulent Plants Plant Pots For Indoor Garden Pots Vegetable Planter Box Outdoor Plants Seed Nursey (Cream)Brand: Yatai DecorIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: Round</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/02eb5d0b-c6dd-47d9-856b-2771aa8d47f6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1ca998d-9a43-4dfe-b8df-1717fd6c2e6a/web/1_1736414981497.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>58.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094872262949</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5616182720</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Artificial Brazil Plant About 1.2 Meters – Artificial Brazil Tree With Plastic Pot</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height – 120cm, Diameter – 95cm, Pot Size: Height – 21cm, Diameter – 24cm. High-Quality Material: Nearly natural PVC plastic branches, and plastic pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7004ca4d-a851-4213-bf3e-0a7020ecc263</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b9b68903-d881-452e-a2e8-9caed277f725/web/1_1736415472603.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98.99 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0056161827208</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1986670169</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Wooden Fence Portable Expanding Wicker Wooden Fence for Home</g:title>
      <g:description>APPROXIMATE SIZE: Fully Expanded- Height – 156cm, Length – 74cm, Close Size- Height – 82cm, Length – 26cm. Can expand and fold to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. DESIGN: The best quality wooden material provides soft and comfortable visual feeling. Beautifully designed wooden fence will enhance your existing decor. YATAI portable expanding wooden fence is perfect for growing climbing plants like ivy or climbing roses, tomatoes and cucumbers. CHILDREN PROTECTION: Isolate your pet dog from your baby or keep your baby away from the dangerous area: fireplace, stairs, safer and more convenient. SAVE SPACE: Expendable isolation gate convenient for your using and take less store space. Opens, closes, expands and contracts with one hand, Swings open and close for easy walk-through. EASY MOVEMENT: Lightweight design for easy movement. You can move this wooden fence to any ideal place without much efforts. It is also convenient to carry. Ideal for home and travel.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/03ff3d15-24d0-49b5-9566-f76ed3a3328d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7a1d7c96-a54a-4328-8f82-3d5f5f1d3f48/web/1_1736411618278.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>300 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019866701693</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7954544482</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Outdoor Portable Greenhouse Walk in 2 Tiers 4 Shelves</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: 200 x 140 x 70 cm, our 2 tier 2 Sided greenhouse is compact with ample shelving making it suitable for indoor and outdoor use. Material: Heavy-duty rust-resistant steel tubes for extended durability, strong enough to hold seed trays, pots and plant growth light. Spacious Inside Space: Constructed with 2-tiers on each side of the greenhouse,total 4 shelves making perfect space for all your blooming flowers, sprouting plants and fresh vegetables. Easy Assembly: You can easily assemble with no tools required. Storage is a breeze too, the indoor outdoor greenhouse can be easily folded up and be put it in basement when you've finished using it. It only occupies a small area. Designed with a zippered roll-up door for easy access and screened ventilation for optimum air circulation. You can place the portable greenhouse on a balcony, deck, patio, or encased porch.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3308690-2443-45b6-9cb7-13a234f92289</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e99ea635-3687-4929-92ce-28af33f2f92a/web/1_1736411910956.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>197.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079545444822</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5520954534</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Concrete Planter Box Rectangular Shape Indoor Garden for Outdoor living room Grow Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>Size: Height-61cm, Diameter-24cm, Length-61cm. (Plant is not included). 💐 Minimalist Rectangular Design: Our concrete vase features a sleek and minimalist rectangular design, adding a touch of modern elegance to your indoor and outdoor spaces. 🌼 Ideal for Home and Office: Whether used as a standalone accent piece or as part of a larger arrangement, our vase is perfect for enhancing the decor of any home or office environment. 🌞 Outdoor Garden Enhancement: Transform your outdoor garden or porch with our versatile planter, ideal for adding greenery and charm to your outdoor living space. 🌿 Versatile Planter: Perfect for a variety of plants including indoor ferns, shrubs, succulents, and more, our vase serves as a versatile planter for enhancing your home, office, or garden decor. 🌸 Perfect for Indoor Plants: Showcase your favorite indoor plants in style with our vase, creating beautiful botanical displays that elevate the ambiance of any room. 🌿 Durable Construction: Crafted from high-quality concrete, our vase is built to last and withstand the elements, making it suitable for both indoor and outdoor use.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f28c9081-830b-4428-8225-dca90e15e890</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/24894b19-b3bc-4f7e-a471-7dbfbe872a04/web/1_1736413946455.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>210 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055209545340</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9884605554</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Umbrella Parasol With Granite Stand Tilt Balcony Waterproof Sunshade For Garden Outdoor </g:title>
      <g:description>YATAI Umbrella Parasol With Granite Stand Tilt Balcony Waterproof Sunshade For Garden Outdoor Patio Use Umbrella Parasol With Stand Garden Parasol Base Beach Umbrella UV Protection Outdoor FurnitureOverall Dimension: Total Height – 248cm, Diameters – 308cm, Base Size: Height – 60cm, Length - 40cm, Width - 60cm. Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol Umbrella with base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1c64a6bb-27e4-4cd5-a143-b7750edf1cf2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3ce3fd75-8b2b-48de-8eaa-f06cc56fef59/web/1_1736412121007.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>385.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098846055544</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9553826287</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor YATAI Wood Sun Lounger Outdoor - Wooden Deck Chair Adjustable Recliner Patio Chairs</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height - 75cm, Width - 65cm, Length - 110cm, (comfortably seat with cushion. Naturally resists termites, rot, decay &amp;amp; moisture. Strong &amp;amp; Durable: Made of hardy wood, oil finishing, strong and durable. Cushion made of 100% polyester fabric. Removable canvas allows for easy washing. Built To Last: Built with weather elements in mind, our sturdy wood construction is made of weather-resistant wood and durable canvas. The material is waterproof and dries quickly. Timeless Gift: Surprise somebody with this awesome outdoor furniture piece! The outdoor chaise is perfect for enjoying the summer weather. Comfortable: Our sun loungers are ergonomic and made of skin-friendly fabrics. The adjustable backrest allows you to choose from 3 levels of personalized comfort, you can lay down on your stomach to enjoy sunbath. Perfect For Outdoors: This relaxing chair is perfect for patios, decks, lawns, poolside and outdoors for enjoying sunshine, having a rest, chatting with your friends or holding party.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/27bbc5e9-9dd1-407d-9f21-37d311d3bd88</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2a429236-47d8-4a49-990b-ddc2a8e5205f/web/1_1736412317884.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>215.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095538262877</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9213758867</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Round Umbrella UV Protection Waterproof Sunshade Beach Umbrella Without Stand </g:title>
      <g:description>Overall Dimension: Total Height – 210cm, Diameters – 162cmDesign: The classic design of this YATAI parasol Umbrella without base will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. High-Quality Material: Umbrella is made with high-quality waterproof, UV protection and fade-resistant fabric, aid in preventing sun-induced skin damage, to last for years of enjoyment. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Usage: Designed to provide shade from sun &amp;amp; protection from rain while you spend your time outdoors. Ideal for your garden, backyard or patio setting. When not in use or in inclement weather, we advise storing the parasol in a cool and dry indoor place.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/09344685-d9cc-40ef-9b3c-47e727201e8f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fe8514f8-aa3f-4f3a-93c3-a49f1aaa9ff9/web/1_1736413157662.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>96 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0092137588674</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7495416549</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Nearly Natural Adams Needle Plant Plant, Lifelike Artificial Plants with Pots</g:title>
      <g:description>About this item🌿 Realistic Detailing: From its textured leaves to its natural-looking pot, every detail of this fake yucca plant has been carefully crafted to mimic the beauty of real foliage. 🌱 Maintenance-Free: Say goodbye to watering, pruning, and wilting leaves. This artificial yucca plant is maintenance-free, allowing you to enjoy its beauty year-round without any upkeep. 🌿 Indoor &amp;amp; Outdoor Use: Bring the outdoors in or add a touch of greenery to your outdoor space. This versatile artificial plant is suitable for both indoor and outdoor environments. ☀️ UV Resistant: Designed to withstand the sun's harsh rays, this artificial plant features UV-resistant green leaves that won't fade or discolor, making it suitable for both indoor and outdoor use. 💪 Sturdy Construction: Built to last, this artificial yucca plant features a sturdy design that ensures it remains upright and stable wherever you choose to display it. 🌱 Easy to Display: Simply place this faux yucca plant in any room or area that could use a pop of greenery. No need for special care or maintenance—just sit back and enjoy its beauty. 🌱 Lifelike Appearance: Enjoy the beauty of lush greenery without the hassle of maintenance. This lifelike yucca plant closely resembles its natural counterpart, adding a touch of botanical charm to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5a94844f-04b0-4c2f-8671-8ceea31fea10</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a9bec1af-d8f3-43ca-9fee-211f45beb6b4/web/1_1736413355195.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>106.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074954165498</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9462500087</g:id>
      <g:title>RAINTREE Garden Fence for Climbing Pots Flowers Plant | Garden Fence Wall for Outside</g:title>
      <g:description>Rustic Elegance: Elevate your garden with the rustic elegance of this wooden fence, adding a charming touch to your outdoor space. Standing Rustic Plant Support: Not just a fence, but a multifunctional plant support that adds structure and style to your garden, supporting your plants in a rustic manner. Spaced Picket Design: The spaced picket design not only enhances the fence's aesthetics but also allows for airflow, creating a well-ventilated and visually appealing garden. Privacy Screen for Balcony: Enjoy added privacy on your balcony with this wooden fence, providing a serene and intimate atmosphere for your outdoor retreat. Money Plant Haven: Create a dedicated space for your money plant to flourish, as this fence serves as the perfect support for its growth and adds a green touch to your garden. Garden Decor Focal Point: Transform your garden into a captivating haven by making this wooden fence the focal point of your garden decor. Easy to Install and Move: Designed for convenience, this fence is easy to install and move, allowing you to effortlessly enhance different areas of your garden or balcony.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f6862cd5-df9f-4d84-a00a-eb360a13e723</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fecf1231-7212-4f22-91ce-4bcac7aa80b4/web/1_1736412882414.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094625000873</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3391556225</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Artificial Areca Palm Tree, 1.5m Lifelike Artificial Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>🌳 Durable &amp;amp; Long-Lasting: Crafted for durability, this artificial tree is designed to maintain its beauty for years to come. 🌿 Natural Charm: Add a touch of nature to your living space with lifelike artificial leaves and greenery. 🌿 Customizable Usage: Use as wall decor or room decor, bringing a refreshing tropical vibe to any space. 🌱 Odorless &amp;amp; Eco-Friendly: Made from high-quality materials, these fake plants are odorless and environmentally friendly. 💧 No-Maintenance: Enjoy the lush greenery without the need for watering or upkeep, perfect for busy lifestyles. 🏡 Versatile Decor: Enhance your indoor environment with the tropical charm of this faux Areca palm tree. 🛏️ Bedroom &amp;amp; Living Room Decor: Create a tranquil ambiance in your bedroom or living room with this realistic artificial palm tree.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/566c2cc3-2b4b-473c-a6ad-addc1c656da2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c8bfbd9e-d750-4926-be5c-f433f1653ac9/web/1_1736414503559.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>224.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033915562257</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8533995249</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Solid Wood Garden Arbor Arch with Trellis Sides – Rustic </g:title>
      <g:description>🌱 Generous Dimensions: With a height of 230 cm and a width of 148 cm, this arbor provides a grand and inviting entrance for any space. 🌱 Premium Solid Wood Construction: Crafted from high-quality solid wood, this garden arbor is durable, weather-resistant, and built to last. Its sturdy design ensures stability, even in outdoor environments. 🌱 Elegant Trellis Sides: The trellis panels on either side provide ample support for climbing plants like roses, ivy, or wisteria, making it ideal for creating a lush and natural canopy. 🌱 Versatile Design: Perfect for various occasions, including weddings, farmhouse entrances, garden pathways, villa courtyards, or as a decorative centerpiece in your backyard. 🌱 Multi-Functional: Use it as an entrance arch, garden gate, or decorative focal point while supporting climbing plants for a picturesque natural display. 🌱 Easy to Assemble: Comes with clear instructions and all necessary hardware for quick and hassle-free installation.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28639cc5-1015-4ea8-a6f5-40e7c682ae9f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/96411087-730b-49d1-8669-6280db9e139f/web/1_1736414764256.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>385.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085339952497</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5855083831</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Elegant Modern Concrete Vase, Stylish Finish Plant Pot with Drainage Hole Durable</g:title>
      <g:description>Size: Height-36cm, Diameter-32cm. (Plant is not included). 💐 Sleek Contemporary Design: Elevate your decor with our elegant modern concrete vase, featuring a stylish textured white finish that adds sophistication to any setting. 🌿 Versatile Plant Pot: Our plant pot is suitable for both indoor and outdoor plants, making it perfect for displaying flowers, succulents, and other greenery in any environment. 🌿 Durable Construction: Crafted from high-quality concrete, our vase boasts a durable and sturdy design that ensures long-lasting use, both indoors and outdoors. 🏡 Ideal for Home Decor: Whether used in the living room, bedroom, or office, our floor vase adds a touch of elegance and style to any interior space. 🌸 Perfect for Flower Arrangements: Display fresh flowers and floral arrangements in our vase to create stunning centerpieces for weddings, parties, and special events. 🎉 Wedding Decor Essential: Incorporate our modern concrete vase into your wedding decor for a chic and sophisticated look that complements any wedding theme. 🌼 Versatile Room Decor: Whether placed on a tabletop, shelf, or mantel, our vase serves as a versatile decor piece that enhances any room's ambiance.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5bbefdfb-e2c6-4939-90f1-a0002c11f8e4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e1119d96-d88a-4f71-82d5-63b7b2bc3a05/web/2_1736415863370.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0058550838314</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4923364236</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Solid Wood Garden Bridge Classic Wooden Arch with Safety Rails Stained Finished</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Length – 143cm, Width – 63cm, Height 43cm. High-Quality Material: Long-lasting material and firewood construction prevents rot, cracking, and splitting, higher quality ensures longer product lifetime. Decorative &amp;amp; Functional: Acts as a walkway between streams and lakes, or simply a beautiful ornament placed in your garden and outdoor areas. Weather-resistance durable fire wood, stained finished beautiful and rustic decoration. Beautifully arched Chinese bridge to highlight your rock garden or pond. Supported by two full length floor joists, mildly arched flooring is durable and easy to walk on. Easy to Assemble: The package comes with all necessary installation tools and materials. All accessories are labeled, manual with detailed installation steps, simple and clear instructions, making installation an easy job for you.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3f78e6b1-ba3a-4697-bab8-4736a3731a3c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/192e2e67-302d-4012-8b9b-211b6b2583db/web/1_1736416424510.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>522 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049233642366</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1884836001</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Elegant Modern Concrete Vase, Stylish Finish Plant Pot with Drainage Hole Durable</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Approx. Length - 90cm, Height - 180cmHigh-Quality Material: Made with High quality pure solid wood maintenance-free weather resistant Eco-friendly. It comes with a wooden stand. The wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front yard and garden area decoration or any other place. Assembles and installs with relative ease- little to no digging required compared to a normal one. Simply insert included pointed stakes into the ground or use a cordless drill and auger bit in hard groundYATAI fences are excellent as a divider and climbing nail support. Use them as fences, divider, pedestrian, walkway fence, or trellis. These fences are extremely durable, so count on them to enhance your garden for many years to come.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5d699770-2d4f-4a17-a185-1b3a8c2bec56</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ecc7f758-0a49-4d53-b3ed-77789bed3404/web/3_1736416171902.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>189 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018848360019</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7025880325</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wholesale Bamboo Wooden Fence with Artificial Plants Green Ivy Leaves Expandable</g:title>
      <g:description>Approximate Size: Height – 126cm, and Length – 180cm. Can expand and fold to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. Features &amp;amp; Uses: The green leaves wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place. Design: The best quality wooden material provides soft and comfortable visual feeling. Beautifully designed wooden fence will enhance your existing decor. YATAI portable expanding wooden fence is perfect for growing climbing plants like ivy or climbing roses, tomatoes and cucumbers. Save Space: Expendable isolation gate convenient for your using and take less store space. Opens, closes, expands and contracts with one hand, Swings open and close for easy walk-through. EASY MOVEMENT: Lightweight design for easy movement. You can move this wooden fence to any ideal place without much efforts. It is also convenient to carry. Ideal for home and travel.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2749388b-9080-451d-8585-47e640c04f9b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/09b57d68-129c-4595-ad1c-46c4baf33dee/web/1_1736416630168.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>45 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070258803258</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8505760887</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Artificial Palm Tree 1.5 meter high - Artificial Palm Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height – 150cm, Diameter – 110cm, Pot Size: Height – 21cm, Diameter – 23. 5cm. High-Quality Material: Nearly natural PVC plastic branches, and plastic pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/31f6ce0c-c72b-430b-9621-388b316431b4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6784eedb-6856-4d9e-be2e-812f1eaabaad/web/1_1736417757422.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>140.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085057608874</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9707873827</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Green Artificial Grass Carpet,decoration floor,garden item</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand: YATAIMaterial: Plastic, It is UV stabilized. 100% recyclable. Size: 2 square meters (200x100cm). It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water. Ideal for areas near swimming pools, golf, and cricket courts and for landscaping, indoor/outdoor garden decoration.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/491d3120-6b21-443a-83b6-2ef2e2645681</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c72b9f99-8911-4f27-91cf-4da0cfd83222/web/1_1736417944645.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>78 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0097078738270</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9300963582</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor 45mm Artificial Grass Carpet Fake Grass Mat - Realistic  Thick Turf Lawn Rug Carpet</g:title>
      <g:description>Material: It is made of super-strong high-density polyethylene that's soft and lush, UV-proof, weather resistant, low-maintenance, providing you with year-round green and turf enjoyment. Multi-Purpose Use: You can put it in your balcony, dining room, backyard, terrace, swimming pools, patio, or make your own golf putting green and baseball playground. Indoor/Outdoor Kids Play Area: This grass carpet is designed for both indoor and outdoor use. Place it in the entryway of your home, living room, bathroom, kitchen or school, play area. Also used as mat, carpet in indoor. Environmentally Friendly: It is soft and comfortable, no irritating odor. You can step on barefoot; it does not hurt your feet. Easy Installation/Customized Size: We can customize any size that you need for you! YATAI Artificial Grass Carpet comes in a roll which is ready made in the size marked above. You only need to choose an area to put and roll out the grass and you are done! You can even cut the grass roll into your sizes to better accommodate your place. It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b1b49783-8e7b-4685-a73f-1e618cb21183</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5da3fd40-eddc-4392-a725-67cf6106fd65/web/1_1736422300498.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>936 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0093009635823</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3025374090</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Round Parasol Tilt Umbrella For Balcony Waterproof Sunshade For Garden</g:title>
      <g:description>Overall Dimension: Total Height – 200cm, Diameters – 265cm. Design: The classic design of this YATAI parasol Umbrella will allow you to transform any area of your garden into a shaded oasis. High-Quality Material: Umbrella is made with high-quality waterproof, UV protection and fade-resistant fabric, aid in preventing sun-induced skin damage, to last for years of enjoyment. Umbrella Rod: This umbrella stand is equipped with an adjustable piston, which can adjust according to the thickness of umbrella post. Usage: Designed to provide shade from sun &amp;amp; protection from rain while you spend your time outdoors. Ideal for your garden, backyard or patio setting. When not in use or in inclement weather, we advise storing the parasol in a cool and dry indoor place.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9978cd42-826d-42de-a737-0a9e9cc02baa</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/58ab4a4c-ec71-4514-ac1c-fe0f47301862/web/1_1736417377523.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>294.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0030253740903</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1725602905</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Acacia Wood Chairs Table Square Bistro Set Patio Dining Table Set 5 Pcs Wood Furniture</g:title>
      <g:description>Premium Acacia Wood Construction: Crafted from high-quality acacia wood, known for its natural resistance to wear and tear, this dining set offers durability and a beautiful wood grain finish that complements various decor styles. Space-Saving Design: Designed with convenience in mind, the folding dining table and chairs allow for effortless storage and portability, making it an ideal choice for compact spaces, outdoor gatherings, or flexible seating arrangements. Comfortable Seating: The set includes four ergonomically designed chairs, ensuring optimal comfort and support, whether you're enjoying a leisurely meal or engaging in extended conversations. Versatile Application: Perfect for a range of settings, from gardens and balconies to poolside areas and office spaces, this dining set serves as a versatile and stylish addition to both indoor and outdoor environments.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cfeefdf8-f7c0-436b-a2bd-aa606744f4af</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/278bb200-24cd-4da7-8853-e20258bb380f/web/1_1736419781224.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>750 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017256029051</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2677716324</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Fake Ficus Plant 2.1 Meters High Ficus silk Plant</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor Fake Ficus Plant 2. 1 Meters High Ficus silk Plant with Plastic Pot &amp;amp; Moss Grass Tall Green plant for Home Garden Decoration – Fake Tree – Artificial PlantsHeight-14cm, Diameters-17cm. Material: Nearly Natural (PVC Plastic), moss grass with Plastic Pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. YATAI’s ficus tree/plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial plants, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4d745bbd-35e4-4918-8656-214acf5e3571</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/635eb88c-8163-488f-b7f2-19cabff339dd/web/1_1736416813272.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>172.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026777163243</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8346660149</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Wholesale 12 Pcs Bamboo Wooden Fence with Artificial Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>APPROXIMATE SIZE: Fully Expanded- Height – 60cm, Length – 220cm, Close Size- Height – 120cm, Length – 40cm. Can expand and fold to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. The greenleaves wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place. DESIGN: The best quality wooden material provides soft and comfortable visual feeling. Beautifully designed wooden fence will enhance your existing decor. YATAI portable expanding wooden fence is perfect for growing climbing plants like ivy or climbing roses, tomatoes and cucumbers. SAVE SPACE: Expendable isolation gate convenient for your using and take less store space. Opens, closes, expands and contracts with one hand, Swings open and close for easy walk-through. PACKAGE INCLUDED: 12 Pcs</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ecd719b-7483-4595-a54a-42e833a7fba9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3b09f0a3-a8c5-4f22-bbf8-3f7dd97658ea/web/1_1736422950717.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>389.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083466601493</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8458411502</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Nearly Natural Artificial Ficus Plant 1.8 Meters High Artificial Tree In Plastic </g:title>
      <g:description>Sizes: Height – 180cm, Diameters – 90cm. Material: Nearly Natural (PVC Plastic), Moss grass, Plastic Pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/552ffe54-21d7-4d6e-9744-5d61a06bafee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b4b50c34-bfb8-433e-913b-44ec03af7f72/web/1_1736417037089.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>153 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084584115022</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6517012507</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Rocking Chair Modern Wooden Rocking Chair with Seating Cushions</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height - 90cm, Width - 63cm, Length - 86cm, (comfortably seat with cushion. Naturally resists termites, rot, decay &amp;amp; moisture. Material: Made of premium solid wood with protective layer of painting, which is weather-resistant and durableComfort: Rocking chair of ergonomic shape, with its contoured seat, wide arms and thickly high-resilience sponge cushion, provides a relaxing place to sit. Multi-purpose : Widely used in Indoor, outdoor, Porch, Patio, Home, Bedroom, Living Room, Den, Terrace, Front Porch, Garden, Deck. Easy to Assemble: This rocker chair is concise in design and can be assembl</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/540b2059-9551-4f2b-acc7-0b29d22a694c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/977546a9-01bc-4b6a-8e10-c03f5148e14b/web/1_1736423586972.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>433 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0065170125076</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1747072627</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Nearly Natural Artificial Banana Tree 2 Meters High With Black Plastic</g:title>
      <g:description>Size: Height – 200cm, Diameter – 116cm. Pot Size: Height – 15cm, Diameters – 17cm. Material: Nearly natural PVC material, plastic pot. Made it high-quality and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/45754848-0e66-4168-a0fb-7b5461eb7ed3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f79ff62-35b5-4927-9db9-c8c7b17602e5/web/1_1736423771462.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>328.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017470726279</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1642300938</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Solid Acacia Wood Sun Lounger With Tyres Outdoor Adjustable Recliner Patio Chairs </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height - 33cm, Width - 60cm, Length-186cm. Naturally resists termites, rot, decay &amp;amp; moisture. Strong &amp;amp; Durable: Made of hardy Acacia wood, oil finishing, strong and durable. Built To Last: Built with weather elements in mind, our sturdy wood construction is made of weather-resistant wood and durable canvas. Timeless Gift: Surprise somebody with this awesome outdoor furniture piece! The outdoor chaise is perfect for enjoying the summer weather. Comfortable: Our sun loungers are ergonomic and made of skin-friendly fabrics. The adjustable backrest allows you to choose from 5 levels of personalized comfort, you can lay down on your stomach to enjoy sunbath. Perfect For Outdoors: This relaxing chair is perfect for patios, decks, lawns, poolside and outdoors for enjoying sunshine, having a rest, chatting with your friends or holding party. Assembly Instructions Included: Packaged with detailed, step-by-step assembly instructions.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f9e4646-7327-4c0c-a59f-bf8ede3cfc8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/14882a55-0f30-44f8-91ca-96c43097a021/web/1_1736423917741.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>502.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016423009384</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8490352768</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor 4Pcs 40 x 60 Cm Size Artificial Boxwood Hedges Panels, Green Ivy Privacy Fence </g:title>
      <g:description>DIMENSIONS: There are 4 pieces (40 x 60cm) panels in each box. PREMIUM QUALITY: Panels could last Longer outdoor! All the panels and leaves are UV resistant, water &amp;amp; wind proof, eco-friendly. Made from high quality 100% FRESH PE Plastic. No poison no smelling materials are completely safe for kids and pets. Also It touches soft and looks realistic. EASY INSTALLATION: Could be easily cut and concected into any shapes, sizes you want. MULTIPLE USAGES: You can DIY all kinds of facades outdoor or indoor. Good solution to protect your privacy, decorate wedding party or other event backdrops, outdoor landscaping designs, garden fences.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ef42681-6ed3-4c52-85cb-82afb8ed25dd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/afb1d8e3-8cc5-4f04-861c-55954807393d/web/1_1736412626881.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084903527680</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7257487551</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Pack of 2 Golden Plastic Garden Fence Plants Flower Bed Edging Interlocking Panels Antiseptic</g:title>
      <g:description>Approximate Size: Total Height – 60m, Length – 52cm, Thickness – 1cm. Material: Plastic, environmental protection, moisture-proof and anti-UV. Design: Beautiful simple style appearance, high quality, lightweight, sturdy and durability for last for years. YATAI portable wooden fence can be used as garden fence, partition wall as an ivy, vine, roses and other climbing plants growing aid of various. Versatile Uses: Perfect for gardens, landscaping, flowerbeds, courtyard, paths, border and lawns, or flower planting. The wooden panel fits any contour for custom landscaping, around trees, flower beds, bushes, garden, yard, and more can be used to decorate your outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place. Our Plastic fence edging rolls are a very decorative way to enhance the look of any garden. They can be used as a separation of your walkway or front garden, but they are also very suitable as a planter to enrich your garden or balcony.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0e33bc23-2dae-47ad-8c9e-f7999cbe8061</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f560edaa-6bed-44ba-bc4f-47e978071eeb/web/1_1736415217597.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>69 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0072574875513</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9498821726</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Natural Round Wood Slices 190mm For Crafts With Hole Blank Wood Plaques for DIY</g:title>
      <g:description>Perfect Size: YATAI’s Wooden slices measure 19cm in diameter, and 1cm in thickness. 100% Natural Wood Material: These natural round wood pieces are made of high-quality, non-toxic and odorless natural wood. There are no splinters and cracks on both sides. The surface is flat, smooth and sturdy enough to paint, color, write, dye and carve. Smooth Surface Corner: The wood slices are got by laser cutting technology. The edge is finished well. They won't scratch your hand and you don't have to sand them. The blank square wood cutouts have round corner to avoid harm caused by pointed corner. Create Handicrafts: These blank wood board are perfect for DIY projects. You can use them to make scrabble tiles, coasters, gift tag, wish card, wood burning crafts and whatever you want. They are perfect for Christmas tree decoration, Halloween, party and home. Wide Uses &amp;amp; Easy To Use: Enough for your unique craft projects. Use for drawing on, or as a base for a centerpiece or decoration. You can write, sculpt, paint on the smooth wood slices. Every slice was drilled with small hole for you to hang easily.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cb1cb993-0793-44ce-98a2-af5c3abcdec4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/068ff130-c77d-497b-920a-fb60f3c922af/web/1_1736422451576.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>39.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0094988217260</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7811729250</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Bamboo Wooden Expandable Wicker Fence with Artificial Green Leaves - 2 Pieces</g:title>
      <g:description>APPROXIMATE SIZE: Fully Expanded- Height – 60cm, Length – 220cm, Close Size- Height – 120cm, Length – 40cm. Can expand and fold to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. The orange leaves wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place. DESIGN: The best quality wooden material provides soft and comfortable visual feeling. Beautifully designed wooden fence will enhance your existing decor. YATAI portable expanding wooden fence is perfect for growing climbing plants like ivy or climbing roses, tomatoes and cucumbers. SAVE SPACE: Expendable isolation gate convenient for your using and take less store space. Opens, closes, expands and contracts with one hand, Swings open and close for easy walk-through.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/aa3d2a95-3ab3-44f7-8587-08703b11a409</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/33477299-5857-470a-a2a1-64c002995895/web/1_1736422643842.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>51.56 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078117292502</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9061330796</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Bamboo Wooden Expandable Wicker Fence with Artificial Green Leaves - 2 Pieces</g:title>
      <g:description>APPROXIMATE SIZE: Fully Expanded- Height – 60cm, Length – 220cm, Close Size- Height – 120cm, Length – 40cm. Can expand and fold to various lengths and heights for different needs in the garden. The orange leaves wooden fence can be used to decorate your home outdoor decoration, front/backyards and garden area decoration or any other place. DESIGN: The best quality wooden material provides soft and comfortable visual feeling. Beautifully designed wooden fence will enhance your existing decor. YATAI portable expanding wooden fence is perfect for growing climbing plants like ivy or climbing roses, tomatoes and cucumbers. SAVE SPACE: Expendable isolation gate convenient for your using and take less store space. Opens, closes, expands and contracts with one hand, Swings open and close for easy walk-through.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/be4566b5-086b-4e6c-8f79-a786d9317d68</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b3e8b488-5f44-4457-bc0f-70f5e3bc3243/web/1_1736423277810.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>51.56 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090613307962</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4503988667</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI WELCOME Sign Wooden Board - House Warming - Rustic Welcome Sign</g:title>
      <g:description>SIZE: YATAI Wood Sign measures 76cm x 63cm x 38cmMATERIAL: YATAI wooden sign has an intentional rustic distressed vintage primitive look. made of high-quality woodThis sign is versatile and will suit many wedding and party styles including country elegant formal casual backyard country and western modern farmhouse and more. Sign may also be appropriate for anniversaries birthdays bridal showers parties and more. This sign makes a great photo prop for wedding and engagement photo shoots. Also great for ring bearer or flower girl to carry down the aisle.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/60eaa232-f7a8-41f3-9deb-62cc73dccaff</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a461a9ca-c01a-40eb-9ea8-a734dc21ead6/web/1_1736423433787.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>53.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045039886676</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9165478238</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Pack of 10 Wooden Decking Tiles - Hardwood Wood Flooring Deck </g:title>
      <g:description>Available at a lower price from other sellers that may not offer free Prime shipping. Dimension: Length – 31cm, Width – 31cm, Thickness – 3cm. High-Quality &amp;amp; Durable: YATAI’s Deck tiles are made from 100% solid Acacia wood, non-slip, waterproof, UV resistant, sanded and oiled for a stunningly smooth finish. Simple Operation: Save time &amp;amp; energy with these easy-to-use interlocking patio tiles. Very fast installation, no fixtures, no adhesives, no skills, you can create your own designs and patterns. Unique filigree design and proven construction with 12 slats per tile and with click / interlocking function. Can be easily disassembled and clicked back again. Wide Range of Uses: It can be used for terraces, balconies, patio, old deck areas, corridors, office buildings, tents, pavilions, hot tubs, parties, events, exhibitions, garages and other uses. It can also be used to cover tired terraces or old decorated suite areas.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/14155918-b9e7-4933-bd61-da2cf2ba21c4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/592efd19-f0ae-4b50-a24c-61d0664dd064/web/1_1736424412536.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>135 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091654782381</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4950458363</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor 30Mm Artificial Grass Carpet Green For Home Outdoor Front</g:title>
      <g:description>Yatai Decor 30Mm Artificial Grass Carpet Green For Home Outdoor Front/Backyards Garden Decoration - Artificial GrassBrand: YATAIMaterial: PlasticSize: 2 square meter (200x100cm). It is easy to install with normal carpet glue and easy to clean with water. Ideal for areas near swimming pools, golf, and cricket courts and for landscaping, indoor/outdoor garden decoration.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b78931db-6dc1-4c44-830f-c95dd1ab6dae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/93968171-65ad-43e3-b49e-b1ae4a3f8b00/web/1_1736425324048.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049504583633</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8097820180</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Luxurious Potted Bonsai Tree, 70cm Lifelike Artificial Plants with Pots</g:title>
      <g:description>About this item🌳 Lifelike Evergreen Elegance: Elevate your living space with the timeless beauty of this 65cm artificial bonsai tree, designed to enhance any room with its lifelike appearance. 🏡 Enhance Your Decor: Add a touch of greenery to your home or office decor with this luxurious artificial plant, bringing the beauty of nature indoors without the need for maintenance. ♻️ Eco-Friendly &amp;amp; Maintenance-Free: Enjoy the benefits of greenery without the hassle of watering or upkeep. This eco-friendly artificial bonsai tree requires no maintenance, offering long-lasting beauty. 🍃 High-Quality Materials: Made from high-quality materials, this artificial plant is built to last, ensuring years of enjoyment and beauty in your home or office decor. 🌿 Realistic Design: Crafted with attention to detail, this artificial plant features realistic green leaves and a natural-looking trunk, creating an authentic bonsai tree appearance. 🌱 Versatile Decor Accent: Perfect for any room in your home or office, this artificial bonsai tree adds a touch of sophistication to tabletops, shelves, or desks, enhancing your decor effortlessly. 🏢 Office Oasis: Create a calming oasis in your workspace with this maintenance-free artificial plant, providing a refreshing touch of greenery to your desk or office environment.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bdd46ae4-aa7e-4422-9207-e6197efdd70f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ddb9fe3e-6b0c-4ed6-9ec1-0a04e8db5628/web/1_1736424587990.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>175.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080978201807</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8100456604</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Nearly Natural Artificial Ficus Plant 90Cm Tall Tree in Plastic Pot with Moss Grass</g:title>
      <g:description>YATAI Nearly Natural Artificial Ficus Plant 90Cm Tall Tree in Plastic Pot with Moss Grass Arrangement For Home Indoor Outdoor Decoration – Garden Plants OfficeBrand Yatai DecorProduct dimensions 10D x 50W x 90H centimetersColour GreenMaterial PlasticItem package quantity 1About this itemBrand: Yatai DecorMaterial: PlasticNumber of items: 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/93b5ec6f-7ff1-4d4b-a19d-c4050531f028</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3d56e731-48ee-4bb0-84d1-88f1ecbb14fa/web/1_1736426081458.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081004566044</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2550073790</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Artificial Rubber Plant - Artificial Rubber Plant With Plastic Pot </g:title>
      <g:description>High-Quality Material: Nearly natural PVC plastic branches, and plastic pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/48269f21-54fd-47b5-9e2e-0f04fd7a427c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/89b59f18-f897-4363-8736-d007a0ce5b87/web/1_1736425835320.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>184.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0025500737904</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
