<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>8400455599</g:id>
      <g:title>smeg Retro 50's Style Automatic Milk Frother with 8 Functions 0.5 L 500.0 W MFF01BLUK Black</g:title>
      <g:description>8 Frothing functions- Features a one-button control with eight settings-Hot or cold milk with light or thick foam, Hot milk, Hot chocolate, Manual function. Perfect for any type of espresso-based drinks, matcha latte, hot cocoa, chocolate milk, and more!Large capacity- This milk frother heats up 500ml milk for delicious lattes or chocolate milk or froths 250ml foam for luscious cappuccinos or macchiato, for convenient share with your family or friendsNo more burned milk- Unlike other milk frothers, Smeg automatic milk frother comes with the Innovative Induction technology which ensures evenly, and fast heating up that prevents the milk from scorching!Quick &amp;amp; quiet- Heats up and prepares exquisite rich thick milk foam in less than 90 seconds for you to make beautiful café-style coffee drinks arts in the kitchen or living room without great disturbanceStylish design &amp;amp; easy to clean- Smeg milk frother is stylishly designed, adding a sleek and modern look to your kitchen. Non-stick coating jug offers you a no hassle cleaning. Premium High quality milk frother guarantees the smooth texture and best flavor foamy milk for your latte cappuccino</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/82db5f9d-89bf-491f-9d97-5d6a376357b4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/51ac46f8-4822-4273-a11b-987cab4f62b3/web/2_1736596991621.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>789 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0084004555995</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
