<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>8993028959</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Roses Flowers for Multiple Occasions - Purple</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiColour PurpleItem weight 1. 1 PoundsRoom type Office, Living RoomUnit count 1. 0 countAbout this itemExpirable : NoSpecies : ArtificialType : Roses</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/04cb7d16-5cda-47b9-a60e-c4984a1ad90c</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/76bfd66f-fcbd-4d43-a605-2414fabc1fdf/web/1_1736857797052.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0089930289594</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1505699403</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Roses Flowers for Multiple Occasions - White</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour WhiteMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Bunch Rose FlowersMaterial: Silk</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/87c7cae4-2b5b-47f6-b805-d4b3d2478c4a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e0a928e7-a672-4f03-b5b8-9c200ea0daa0/web/1_1736858394355.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015056994036</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2027425943</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Nearly Natural Artificial Plants Orchid Flowers For Multiple Occasions - Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type OrchidColour PinkSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion WeddingAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Orchid FlowersColor: Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c497a9aa-837b-4d1e-9d18-f941a1414d39</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7bcafcf7-7748-4312-a502-b5dcad7d03ac/web/1_1736859724644.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020274259430</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2671111599</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Roses Flowers for Multiple Occasions - Yellow</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour YellowMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Bunch Rose FlowersMaterial: Silk</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d989ca02-e34e-4b8f-934f-6facacbb413f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3c23c81b-007d-48e9-a71a-f766b3e1e0d0/web/1_1736858163344.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0026711115994</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4378779762</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Home Decor, M-Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour Maroon GreenMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product Home Decor, Office DecorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 🌼 Table Centerpiece: Arrange these artificial eucalyptus leaves in a vase or create a stunning table centerpiece for weddings, parties, or everyday decor. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 💐 Realistic Appearance: The faux eucalyptus leaves closely resemble their natural counterparts, providing a realistic and long-lasting alternative to fresh flowers. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/69febf86-8cb1-42a9-91c3-fe0520d8df9b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c5b9c011-3e61-482d-af09-b5effd2f6dfc/web/5_1736852055993.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043787797626</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7361482282</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 5 Heads Silk Hydrangea Flowers Artificial Plants For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use OutdoorAbout this itemBrand: Yatai;Name: Hydrangea Flowers;Color: Cream/Pink;Material: Fabric/Silk;Size: H-50cm, Heads-17cm, Diameter per bunch-25cm ;Heads: 1 bunch &amp;amp; 5 heads ;Uses: It is an ideal arrangement for home decoration, wedding party bridal bouquet, hotels, restaurants, office, and festival decoration. ;Features: It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4dab99e-7888-4521-841e-fb0a9b8d53cb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2cd557e5-5cf8-49b6-babf-4560b2e2ac13/web/1_1736854282981.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073614822825</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7631319740</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Festival Glitter Monstera Leaf Artificial Festival Flowers Decorations Golden Flowers Ornaments – Fake Flowers Bouquets Arrangement Table Centerpieces Floral Wreath Wedding Decor (2)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type MonsteraColour GoldMaterial PlasticRecommended uses for product Indoor Decor, Outdoor Decor, Event Decor, Home Decor, Office Decor, Wedding Decor, Party DecorAbout this itemTotal Height -64cm, Leaf Branch Length - 30cm, stem can be cut easily to fit different vases. Made of high-quality PVC eco-friendly material with bright and vivid gold color, soft touch, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Flowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet. A great decoration for Christmas, arts, crafts, dinner table, wedding, party, birthday, shower, meeting room décor, and anywhere that you want to put. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4f4a9c2e-1322-4b22-940a-a803726151f4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a06b0509-5cdd-49f8-9936-f1195c1f9ca2/web/2_1736859918395.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076313197409</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5577863225</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Purple Real Touch Rose Flowers Bridal Wedding Party Decor Bouquet Artificial Plants - Roses</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour PurpleSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemExpirable : NoSpecies : ArtificialType : Roses</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f46c52dc-3cbb-4630-8d44-4c9a2aedb256</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4bae83d9-3897-42c7-901c-6d8483d7df69/web/1_1736858068511.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055778632250</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8386785206</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Roses Flowers for Multiple Occasions - Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type roseColour PinkMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Bunch Rose FlowersMaterial: Silk</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/416dd033-7471-4e08-a599-f34773cb3032</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a327b7c6-094d-4226-ae25-f645917d1b35/web/1_1736858250838.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0083867852067</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2048433528</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Roses Flowers for Multiple Occasions - Yellow</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type lemonColour YellowMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Bunch Rose FlowersMaterial: Silk</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3b1963a7-cc94-44be-91a7-07b1e514c6d2</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/20d779a0-6e76-4017-874a-9f5881d69e4e/web/1_1736857956107.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020484335283</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7661429578</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Silk Hydrangea Flowers 7/Heads Artificial Plants For Home Party Bridal Wedding Decoration</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion WeddingAbout this itemBrand: Yatai;Name: Hydrangea Flowers;Color: Cream Peach;Material: Fabric/Silk;Size: H-45cm, Head-17cm, Diameter per bunch-28cm ;Heads: 1 bunch &amp;amp; 7 heads;Uses: It is an ideal arrangement for home decoration, wedding party bridal bouquet, hotels, restaurants, office, and festival decoration. ;Features: It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look. ;Made from high-quality materials and vibrant colors.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/63eee9c0-ccfd-469a-8048-7eeba2538c2d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/291ab1c7-d19d-4184-9020-615d0f76e06d/web/1_1736854603327.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0076614295781</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2191921253</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Stainless Steel Electric Kettle With Auto Shutt off and Boil Dry Protection 2 L 1800 W </g:title>
      <g:description>AUTO SHUT-OFF &amp;amp; BOIL-DRY PROTECTION - Automatic shut off function upon boiling and the boil-dry protection prevents it from boiling if there is insufficient water present. CAPACITY 2. 0L - The capacity of this Electric Kettle is 2. 0 L. Large size helps to make multiple cups of tea or coffee. To make pouring comfortable and easy, the kettle features an ergonomic handle. SAFETY LOCK LID, 360° ROTATIONAL BASE - The lid fixes nicely into place and is locked by a safety lock. To keep the kitchen tidy, the base has integrated cord storage so it can be tidied away at your convenience &amp;amp; the handy 360° base means it can be comfortably used by right &amp;amp; left-handed people. STAINLESS STEEL - This Electric Kettle is made of stainless steel and is distinguished by their durability and makes a healthy kitchen appliance to heat up water. Comes With 2 Years Of Manufacturer Warranty. Easy-pour spout makes it easy to pour hot water without making a messOverviewGeepas Gk5466 Cordless Electric Kettle Is A Perfect Addition To Your Kitchen Accessories. It Comes With Locking Lid, Multi-Protection System, Automatic Shut Off Capability And Heat-Resistant Plastic Housing. The Capacity Is 1. 8 Litters At A Time And It Is Really Easy To Use. SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation CountertopProduct Weight 940 gColour Name Silver/BlackWhat's In The Box Electric KettleEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 1. 1 To 2. 5 LAppliance Wattage 1500 To 1850 WattPower Source ElectricNumber of Cups 4 CupProduct Length 5. 2 cmProduct Height 40. 4 cmProduct Width/Depth 52. 8 cmCapacity 2 LWattage 1800 WFeatures Auto Shut Off, Corded, Dishwasher Safe, Indicator Lights, WashableModel Number GK5466BModel Name GK5466B</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/63d6cef3-db58-4724-9a47-ceb1c4ac5072</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5282160e-36d9-4baf-b751-7da5bc2e7e60/web/1_1736852263284.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0021919212537</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3392789029</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 12 Heads Rose's Buds Artificial Plants Silk Rose Flowers</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion WeddingAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose's BudsColor: Light Purple/GreenMaterial: Fabric/SilkSize: Length-32 CentimetersHeads: 1 bunch &amp;amp; 12 headsUses: It is an ideal arrangement for home decoration, wedding party bridal bouquet, hotels, restaurants, office, and festival decoration.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5027ab88-2c2d-4dcb-a7ea-198a666085fc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c4a14f06-c8e8-4e58-87e8-f29864891483/web/1_1736768849384.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033927890294</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9610303542</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 12 Heads Red Rose's Buds Artificial Plants Silk Rose Flowers For Party Wedding Bridal Bouquet</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour PinkMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose's BudsColor: Dark Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a98396c1-a502-4822-b24e-c379afff6200</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/6f040922-9325-44b6-9827-d992664e33d6/web/1_1736768773817.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096103035421</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7374418005</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Pack of 3 Artificial Anthurium Flowers Realistic Fake Flower Bouquet</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiColour RedMaterial RubberSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemDimensions: Total Length - 70cm, Flowers Branch Length – 10cm, Width – 9cm. (Vase not included)High Quality Material: Made of high-quality PVC plastic, and eco-friendly material with bright and vivid color, soft touch, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: This tiny arrangement simple design makes it a clutter-free way to bring life to small living spaces or the perfect desk accessory. Flowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/98910233-3466-4611-9588-a9d26cfb7ee4</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/30587ed2-3692-4220-8be8-a763f0850dcd/web/5_1736769243293.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>20.70 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0073744180055</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3319346133</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Wheat Grass Leaf Fake Shrubs Plants Autumn Faux</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type Wheat GrassMaterial PlasticSpecific uses for product Home DecorIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemTotal Height - 88cm, soft touch, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Plastic wheat bundle is resistant to ultraviolet rays, never fades, can resist storms and sunlight, keeps alive all year round, never wilts, very suitable for any gardening project or decorative style. Wheat grass leaf are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will bring golden light to any environment. Whether it is used for home decor, party decor, wedding decor, you will get a very amazing effect. Golden wheat plant is ideal for home decoration, such as living room, kitchen and bedroom. No matter what season you are in, you can feel the atmosphere of autumn. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/de1d5c1a-753f-4e6f-95ad-7ab5647faa98</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/48cc8de3-1c1f-463d-8b0e-ada1c3143810/web/2_1736769700416.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21.42 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033193461334</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5271346027</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Golden Wheat Grass Leaf Fake Shrubs Plants</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type Wheat GrassMaterial PlasticSpecific uses for product Home DecorIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemTotal Height - 88cm, soft touch, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Plastic wheat bundle is resistant to ultraviolet rays, never fades, can resist storms and sunlight, keeps alive all year round, never wilts, very suitable for any gardening project or decorative style. Wheat grass leaf are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will bring golden light to any environment. Whether it is used for home decor, party decor, wedding decor, you will get a very amazing effect. Golden wheat plant is ideal for home decoration, such as living room, kitchen and bedroom. No matter what season you are in, you can feel the atmosphere of autumn. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c20da54-3022-408a-8360-a29ce108d94d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b40c8adf-db93-489a-8af5-68c21a6bc1a7/web/3_1736769504877.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21.42 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052713460275</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1933447964</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai European Style 6/Heads Luxury Silk Rose Flowers Artificial Plants For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour iceMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersColor: Orange/Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/698e23c5-cbf5-42a9-bdeb-c31898620f32</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2eaa6b0a-9455-4093-9cb1-991330ca4b50/web/1_1736770177190.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0019334479642</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1208288476</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Flowers Bouquet, Elegant Faux Silk Hydrangea Flowers</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour clearMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product Home DecorAbout this itemSize: Bouquet Diameter- 50cm Height-30cm (Not Include decorations)🌸 Elegant Design: Our artificial flowers bouquet features lifelike silk flowers, offering a touch of elegance and charm to any setting. 🌼 Lifelike &amp;amp; Vibrant: Enjoy the beauty of realistic fake flowers that are fade-resistant and vibrant, Perfect for Wedding Decor, Room Decor, Home Decor and Office Decor. 🌿 Durable &amp;amp; Maintenance-Free: These artificial flowers are designed to be long-lasting and require no maintenance, providing a hassle-free decorating solution. 🌺 Versatile Use: Suitable for both indoor and outdoor faux flowers for vase, these fake flower arrangements enhance any space with their realistic appearance. 🎉 Ideal for Events: Perfect for weddings decor, parties, and gifts, our faux flower arrangements add a touch of sophistication to any event. 💐 Perfect for Crafts: Use our artificial flowers for decoration to create stunning flower garlands and DIY projects, adding a personal touch to your decor. 🎁🎄 Gift-Worthy and Festive Decorations: These beautiful flower bouquets make an excellent Mother's Day gift or Valentine's Day surprise, and can also be integrated into your fall decorations &amp;amp; Christmas decorations.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9a8300fa-4fc7-483f-80b6-a9c04c273009</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce5cfa05-d9d6-4fe0-8f2d-6516a9d1fbac/web/1_1736771139190.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21.78 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012082884768</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5786730338</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Flowers with Arrangement and Vase </g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type hydrangeaMaterial Arrangement15Product dimensions 6D x 15W x 35H centimetersSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemHigh Quality Material: High quality silk and eco-friendly soft touch material, natural and realistic, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: You can definitely use this artificial, Peony Flowers in a range of permanent floral arrangements. In a mixed flower design with roses, peonies, and greens, make it the focal point. For a 'white wedding' themed affair, add it to your white centerpieces, or gather a few stems to create a Peony wedding bouquet for the bride. We also love all-hydrangea arrangementsFlowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/893a84d6-c014-4547-8401-04a8aa750ebd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/55a75a2a-cd2a-4cf5-959f-bba864edf5cd/web/2_1736776080277.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0057867303386</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4996429774</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 7 Heads European Style Daisy Flowers Artificial Plants For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type OrangeColour multiMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Daisy FlowersColor: Orange/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/76638158-43ea-44e3-b7b4-98269d987f28</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ee7e708-112e-4aad-b943-742c58817f61/web/1_1736771958644.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049964297743</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8146244863</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Beautiful Silk Artificial Rose Flowers Gift For Anniversary Party Birthday Wedding Decoration</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour YellowMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersColor: Yellow/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c3d8a910-441a-444c-af5e-84a3d71be291</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5e236ef9-84cd-4f44-b2b6-43e5d388e211/web/1_1736772239149.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081462448630</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7979671667</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Silk Hydrangea Flower Bunch Arrangements Large</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour OtherMaterial OtherProduct dimensions 45D x 30W x 35H centimetersAbout this itemSize: Bouquet Diameter- 50cm Height-30cm (Not Include decorations)Material: YATAI Hydrangea Flowers are made of silk, full and soft petals, Natural-looking. Wire wrapped with plastics is used for firmness and angle-adjustable in creating the stems. The beauty of fake hydrangea flowers bouquets is that you can enjoy the look you crave, but don't have to worry about have no time watering, pruning, and other maintenanceRealistic artificial hydrangea flower is suitable for outdoor or indoor decoration, decorating your garden and party, hanging on the wall or doors, placing it on the table and so onUV protected faux flower bouquet made of high-quality plastic and fabric material, bendable, non-toxic and durable for long time use, a brilliant alternative to live planting</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d508e6db-45b9-4b7a-9ff4-045c34e82f6e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/41fabd87-8856-4c35-986f-52b9a98d1534/web/1_1736772324329.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>21.78 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079796716679</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3786354615</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Flowers Stem, Lifelike PVC Plants with Delicate Blossom, Realistic Faux Flowers</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type PlantColour OrangeMaterial Polyvinyl ChlorideProduct dimensions 30D x 30W x 35H centimetersAbout this item🌸 Lifelike &amp;amp; Versatile: These artificial flowers for decoration feature delicate blossoms, perfect for adding a touch of elegance to your home decor, office decor, or any special event. 🌿 Long-Lasting &amp;amp; Maintenance-Free: Enjoy the beauty of flowers artificial for decoration without the hassle. These fake flowers are designed to last, offering a fresh look for table decor or bedroom decor year-round. 🎁 Durable &amp;amp; Realistic: Made from high-quality PVC, these artificial plants with pots offer a realistic appearance that stays beautiful for years, perfect for home decor items for living room. 🌿 Enhance Any Space: These flowers bouquet fresh alternatives are perfect for decoration items for living room and office decor, bringing a vibrant touch of nature indoors. 🏡 Perfect for Vase Filling: These faux flowers are ideal for creating stunning centerpieces or room decoration by filling vases with vibrant, realistic blooms that enhance any space. 🎉 Ideal for Special Occasions: Whether it's for wedding decorations, valentine’s day decorations, or festive Christmas flower decorations, these fake plants bring lasting beauty to any celebration. 🌸 Perfect for DIY &amp;amp; Events: Create stunning centerpieces or unique room decorations with these versatile flowers artificial for decoration, ideal for table decor, wedding decorations, and more.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cc499c5c-bc35-47c6-aeac-2258002daf8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e239220a-31c0-4ecb-a01e-6d12322f8484/web/1_1736775719578.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037863546154</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6622388170</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Rose Hydrangea Flowers Gift For Anniversary Party Birthday Wedding Valentine's Day</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion Wedding, Anniversary, Birthday, Valentine's DayAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose/Hydrangea FlowersColor: Pink/Peach</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/47d775ca-76dc-49a3-bfc2-472cc826141e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fbf2573c-7cec-4b7e-9097-08ce53550615/web/1_1736773169211.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066223881703</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6636188046</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 7 Heads European Style Daisy Flowers Artificial Plants For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type DaisyColour multiMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Daisy FlowersColor: Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6833e3e9-bbc7-4206-a659-f95c3088675b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8e7c9a4b-8fb8-4bcc-ae3b-d887718ec593/web/1_1736772838890.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066361880460</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6772261433</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Orchid Flowers, Elegant Lifelike Phalaenopsis Flowers, Orchid Fake Flowers for Vase Filling, Long-Lasting, No Maintenance Artificial Flowers for Home Office Decor, Ideal Gift, D-Purpl</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type orchidColour PurpleSpecific uses for product Home Decor, Office DecorPackage information VaseAbout this item🌸 Artificial Orchid Flowers: Elevate your space with our elegant and lifelike Phalaenopsis flowers, perfect for adding a touch of sophistication to any setting. 🌿 Long-Lasting and No Maintenance: Enjoy the beauty of fresh flowers without the upkeep. Our artificial orchids are durable and require no maintenance, ensuring lasting charm. 🏡 Versatile Decor: Use these fake flowers for vase filling, table decorations, or as part of a floral arrangement. They're perfect for adding flair to any room or event. ✨ Aesthetic Room Decor: Enhance your bedroom, living room, or any space with these beautiful orchid flowers, creating a serene and elegant ambiance. 🌼 Fade Resistant: Our artificial flowers maintain their vibrant colors over time, ensuring that your decor remains fresh and vibrant. 🌺 Add Charm to Any Setting: Whether you're decorating for a party or simply sprucing up your home, these artificial orchids bring beauty and charm to any setting. 🎉 Perfect for Special Occasions: From Christmas decorations to Ramadan decor, these artificial orchids are a versatile addition to any celebration or holiday theme. 🎁 Ideal Gift: Make your special day even more memorable with these stunning artificial orchids. They also make the perfect gift for weddings, anniversaries, or any occasion.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/28655473-83da-4eae-86c0-5fb7d9ef5818</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e83fe95c-74fe-4209-8489-b7c0b943670b/web/1_1736772436327.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0067722614335</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5561842978</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Rose Hydrangea Flowers Gift For Anniversary Party Birthday Wedding Valentine's Day</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use IndoorAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose/Hydrangea FlowersColor: Red/Maroon</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6dad957b-c04e-4923-a45d-195ccd4860a9</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/57adbf38-fcad-4d67-820b-cb4cda628076/web/1_1736772518228.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055618429781</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7455920906</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Stripe Design Plastic Pot for Flower Filling and Arrangements 2 pcs</g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour COFFEE2Brand YataiProduct dimensions 13L x 13W x 13H centimetersStyle modernAbout this itemMATERIAL: PlasticSTYLE: planterCOLOR: coffeeUNIQUE DESIGN: Thanks to the simple and elegant design, this vase can provide your interior space fresh and clean feeling. The modern and elegant vase with smooth plastic surface and unique openings. HANDMADE HIGH QUALITY: Handmade of high-quality, high grade durable vitreous plastic pot. Each vase is made individually by hand with the slight variations that create a completely unique piece each time. MULTIPUPOSE USES: Great for office or home décor, dinner parties, holidays, wedding planning and other special occasions. YATAI’s vase can provide a sweet and romantic atmosphere in your space without any of the troublesome maintenance. GREAT GIFT: This plastic pot is packaged safely and beautifully so that they can be the best gift to your family or friends who likes to decorate his/her house!</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/a02c8bc3-f8b8-459a-8eda-eccd70cc4260</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dc128346-853a-46f0-a559-97cd9669172f/web/1_1736772810814.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0074559209061</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4207960516</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Plants 2 Bunch Peony Flowers For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type peonyColour PurpleIndoor/outdoor use IndoorOccasion Anniversary, BirthdayAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Peony FlowersColor: Purple/Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8402b21d-d082-4a79-ab40-5e12ab817ac1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/448741aa-17da-475f-84b6-0d31268b43bd/web/3_1736773082095.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042079605168</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4582487873</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai European Style Rose Flowers 7/Heads Artificial Plants For Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour PinkMaterial FabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersColor: Dark Pink</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/25b0093c-5ee9-48f2-b875-d7403f33ae71</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/299a5a64-b30b-4e57-98df-59e2ab82d132/web/1_1736772918794.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045824878732</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6915812094</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai European Style Rose Flowers 7/Heads Artificial Plants For Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour YellowMaterial FabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersColor: Yellow/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9b7d4172-68d3-43d9-a478-002e30cbc6ea</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f08b8250-8311-43f9-8f5f-c2aee99da327/web/1_1736773093381.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0069158120947</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5963478973</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai European Style Rose Flowers 7/Heads Artificial Plants For Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour PinkMaterial FabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersColor: Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b792616b-8e37-4857-93fa-233d8ad53d8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ce332fef-feff-4358-beb6-88794e149b20/web/1_1736772992939.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0059634789737</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6819750039</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Peony Flowers 5 Heads Gift For Anniversary Party Birthday Wedding Valentine's Day</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type PeonyColour BlueMaterial FabricSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Peony FlowersColor: Sky Blue</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/560f668e-471d-4c08-9416-64033ec6f8bc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d1b4506c-bbf0-4830-9616-f793f7716614/web/1_1736773536470.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.39 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068197500390</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9016083791</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Ivy Leaf Garland Artificial Plants Potato Vine Hanging Silk Flowers Garland Fake Foliage Flower Holiday Ornaments Floral Bouquets For Kitchen Mirror Door Swings Party Decoration (1)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type Vine, IvyMaterial SilkProduct dimensions 30D x 30W x 160H centimetersIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemBrand: YATAINumber of items: 1Occasion type: christmasMaterial: SilkIndoor outdoor usage: outdoorPlant or animal product type: Vine</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1b3461de-94f8-4966-9d11-6754727f28fc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9627fdef-0d48-4fb2-9fa9-72149bedaf20/web/2_1736773753279.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090160837912</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3981197494</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI White Mini Cute Plastic Pots For Plants  Flowers Garden Plant (4)</g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour greenSpecial features Drainage HoleStyle ModernShape RoundAbout this itemSize: Height-7. 5cm, Diameter-16cm. Planter does not have drainage holes. High-Quality Material: YATAI’s pot is made of high-quality plastic material, strong and durable, not easy to be deformed or broken. Elegant design and great quality. Features: This YATAI’s planter is an attractive piece on its own. This planter would look great with indoor plants, and flowers. It is not only perfect for flowers, plants, but also can be used in your wedding decor as centerpieces, or any event projects.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/650e3039-9d23-45ee-8917-e3a5a29db7ee</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4a23e958-13fa-4f00-a1bb-76e8366462b9/web/2_1736774403692.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039811974941</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3618090863</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Daisy Flowers Bouquet, Vibrant Silk Lifelike Artificial Flowers for Vases, Elegant  Realistic Fake Flowers for Home Decor, Maintenance Free Faux Daisy Flowers for Decoration, Flesh</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour FleshMaterial SilkProduct dimensions 10D x 25W x 35H centimetersAbout this item🌼 Artificial Daisy: These artificial daisy flowers bring the charm of daisies to your decor, brightening up any space. 🌷 Fake Flower Bouquet: This artificial flower bouquet is perfect for vases, making it a versatile decoration for any space. 🎨 Faux Flowers for Vase: These faux flowers are ideal for vase arrangements, providing a stunning centerpiece for your home or office. 💐 Flower Arrangements: Perfect for creating stunning flower arrangements for home, office, or events. 🌼 Artifical Flowers: These artifical flowers are designed to look like the real thing, bringing elegance to any setting. 🌻 Fake Flowers for Garden: Perfect for garden decoration, these fake flowers add color and beauty to outdoor spaces. 🌼 Fake Flower Arrangement: Create beautiful fake flower arrangements that last forever. 🌿 Faux Flower: These faux flowers offer the beauty of real flowers without the upkeep.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ad9024d-2515-4214-96df-8cb2c624e02f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7a00374a-6097-474a-9236-62a5c2b72407/web/1_1736774247358.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0036180908638</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5307481728</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Butterflies Stakes 11cm Wide Waterproof Artificial Butterfly Stakes Stems Decorations Butterfly Garden Ornament Floral Picks Garden Stakes (12cm, Mix-color-8pcs)</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour Mix-color-8pcsBrand YataiTheme ButterflyMaterial ResinStyle GardenAbout this item❥Sufficient quantity: The package contains 12 pieces monarch butterfly decorations in Mix colors, vibrant color and sufficient quantity to meet your decoration needs and replacements. ❥Durable and practical: These artificial butterfly wall decors are made of quality PVC, plastic and metal, which are durable and practical, not easy to fade and fray, can be applied for a long time, and they are also safe and reliable for people to use. ❥Easy to apply: On the one hand, the YATAI butterfly has a metal on its abdomen, you can place it directly on the Garden or other places, on the other hand, you can stick it on the wall by using the back glue ( Not included), easy way to decorate your home. ❥Realistic butterfly decor: These 3D YATAI butterfly magnet decors look realistic, and they can be applied for decorating many occasions, such as daily party, wedding, bedroom, living room, refrigerator and so on, adding more charming atmosphere. ❥Beautiful gifts: These adorable monarch butterfly decors can be applied as elegant and delicate gifts for family members and relatives, you can also share these butterfly party decorations to your friends who need to decorate their home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0f25bd62-d3c3-45ae-a118-fef66f321a54</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2f0c4275-b0b5-44ef-817e-dee93cc86546/web/1_1736774038422.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>23.40 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0053074817289</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6321379809</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Gray Plastic Pots For Plants  Flowers Garden Plant Container for Cactus Succulents Orchid Flowers House Plants Herbs Foliage Plant Seed Nursery Décor Garden Plant Container (3)</g:title>
      <g:description>Material PlasticColour redSpecial features Drainage HoleStyle ModernShape RoundAbout this itemBrand: YataiIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: RoundBrand: YataiIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticMounting type: TabletopItem shape: Round</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bdc56fe9-272d-4480-9ce0-a7f36f167c8b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/9eb567c3-ae8f-473c-85f3-04fdddea063b/web/2_1736774591750.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063213798096</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1102310377</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Leaf Shaped Plastic Plants Flowers Pots  Planters For Succulent Cactus Orchid Flowers Indoor Outdoor Balcony Garden Decor – Plastic Pots – Flowers Vase – Garden Plant Container (3)</g:title>
      <g:description>Item Package Quantity: 3Material PlasticColour greenStyle GardenShape RoundIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemBrand: YataiIs assembly required: FalseMaterial: PlasticItem shape: Round</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/70f75df9-335c-49af-ab96-f59a1487e5ef</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0dae2242-986c-4ebe-9c9d-8909e2f85ff0/web/1_1736775458393.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.84 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0011023103777</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5175558744</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Flowers, Realistic PVC Succulent Plants with Natural Texture</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type succulentsColour GreenMaterial Polyvinyl ChlorideProduct dimensions 20D x 20W x 30H centimetersAbout this item🌿 Lifelike Succulent Design: These artificial flowers for decoration capture the natural texture of real succulents, offering a vibrant, maintenance-free option for home decor or office decor. 🌸 Long-Lasting &amp;amp; Maintenance-Free: Perfect for room decor and table decor, these fake flowers provide a fresh, lifelike appearance that lasts without any upkeep, ideal for busy homes or offices. 🌺 Elegant Event &amp;amp; DIY Craft Decor: Ideal for table decor and DIY projects, these faux flowers make beautiful centerpieces or crafts for events like weddings, parties, or special gatherings. 🌷 Year-Round Festive Decor: Use these flowers bouquet fresh alternatives for Christmas flower decorations, fall decorations, or diwali flowers, adding a festive touch to your home or office. 🏡 Versatile Home Decor: Whether you're decorating your living room, bedroom, or office desk, these flowers artificial for decoration add a touch of greenery to any space, creating a welcoming atmosphere. 🎉 Perfect for Special Occasions: These artificial plants with pots are perfect for wedding decorations, valentine’s day decorations, or as a thoughtful anniversary gift, bringing lasting beauty to any event. 🌸 Perfect Vase Filler: Fill your vases with these dry flowers for decoration, creating stunning centerpieces or table decor that adds elegance and charm to any room or event.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/57b925d9-7be1-4077-8cfe-be5d06108eab</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1c21f218-dc6d-48fa-a192-fd9a90e626d5/web/1_1736774636412.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.53 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0051755587445</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3776795738</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Orchid Flowers, Premium PU Lifelike Phalaenopsis Flower</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type orangeColour OrangeMaterial PlasticProduct dimensions 8D x 15W x 90H centimetersAbout this itemOnly Flower Vase/Pot is not Included🌼 Fake Plastic Orchid Flowers: Made from high-quality plastic, these fake orchid flowers offer durability and long-lasting beauty without the need for maintenance. 💐 Maintenance-Free Orchid Plant: Say goodbye to watering and upkeep with these maintenance-free faux orchid flowers, perfect for busy lifestyles and hassle-free decor. 🎍 Long Stem Faux Flowers: Featuring long stems, these faux orchids are ideal for creating elegant floral displays in your home, office, or at weddings and special events. 🏡 Home Decor Office Decor: Enhance the ambiance of your home or office with these artificial orchid flowers, adding a touch of natural beauty to any space. 🌟 Versatile Decor Accent: Whether used as a centerpiece, in floral arrangements, or as decorative accents, these orchid flowers effortlessly elevate any room's decor. 🌸 Orchid Artificial Flowers: Elevate your decor with these stunning artificial orchid flowers, crafted to mimic the beauty of Phalaenopsis orchids. 🎁 Weddings Gift: Surprise newlyweds or celebrate special occasions with the gift of these exquisite artificial orchid flowers, a timeless symbol of love and elegance.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/68d7e5d5-9d3b-46fc-8973-3bb054b24e27</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/28f66675-a2c7-4925-a060-6cbff909e1c0/web/2_1736773984559.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0037767957384</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4535284734</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Pack of 4 Natural Dried Pampas Grass Flowers Spray Preserved Plants Flower Wholesale Dried Flowers for Home Table Vase Centerpiece Festival Ornament Wedding Party Decoration (White)</g:title>
      <g:description>Color: WhiteColour WhiteBrand YataiSpecific uses for product otherManufacturer YATAIAbout this itemBrand: YataiUnit count: 4Brand: YATAIUnit count: 4</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bc5a78cd-963e-4344-8902-29f990190e81</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a91ce406-2e71-4d79-945c-82d0d1b21b16/web/2_1736775575695.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0045352847347</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7885696216</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Sakura Flowers, Hanging Sakura Flower with Wire Stem, Realistic Silk Cherry Blossom Flower Arrangement, Long-Lasting  Low Maintenance Fake Flowers for Home Wedding Decor (1, Red)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type Cherry BlossomColour RedMaterial SilkProduct dimensions 60D x 60W x 120H centimetersAbout this itemRealistic Silk Elegance: Revel in the realistic elegance of these silk Sakura flowers, providing a lifelike touch to your decor without the need for constant care. Dry Flowers Alternative: Opt for these artificial Sakura flowers as an alternative to dry flowers, offering the same aesthetic charm without the fragility. Long-Lasting &amp;amp; Low Maintenance: Enjoy the enduring beauty of these fake Sakura flowers, offering a long-lasting and low-maintenance solution for your decorative needs. Valentine Day Charm: Infuse romance and charm into your Valentine's Day celebrations with the delicate and beautiful presence of these artificial Sakura flowers. Versatile Decoration: Ideal for a variety of occasions, these artificial Sakura flowers enhance the beauty of weddings, parties, or everyday home decor. Home Decoration Accent: Accentuate your home decor with these artificial Sakura flowers, providing a refreshing and vibrant aesthetic to your living space. Table Decoration Delight: Elevate your table decorations with the enchanting beauty of Sakura flowers, creating a captivating and visually appealing setting.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d239be5b-1b20-4dfd-9a48-a412146fca63</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/468e03a4-8a8a-43b8-b0aa-c31ac72001bd/web/2_1736775339156.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.98 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0078856962162</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8850251318</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Flameless Candle Battery Operated</g:title>
      <g:description>Finish type PolishedBase material PlasticItem weight 1 KilogramsLamp type Light Emitting DiodeShade colour RedAbout this itemSize: Diameter 3. 5cm and, Length -4. 5cm Material: candles are crafted to perfection with the finest quality materials so you can enjoy unique results. The candles are made with Plastic and Operated by 2 x Butten Cell Batteries that are replicableSAFE TO USE: 100% SAFE! Enjoy all the benefits of traditional candles and none of the negatives! We care about your safety, and a risk of fire shouldn't be a concern. No more dripping-hot wax, no more smoke or worry about falling asleep without blowing out the candlesARE YOU PLANNING A PARTY OR WEDDING? You will love this Battery-Operated Flameless Candles. . . Just set them into your favorite lantern, chandelier, sconce or candle holder or mix with other decorations. Moving Wick and Dancing Flame: flameless taper candles feature realistic looking flameless candles on the market. Light glows and dances on the moving flame piece providing a stunning, real looking effect. No more "static" wicks on your flameless taper candles. This real looking flame taper candles can be used as a great gift as well as a wonderful set for your own home decor and also for restaurant, office, weddings, dinner, parties, children rooms decoration. PACKAGE: 6 PCS (BATTERY INCLUDED)</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/88990dd4-ae36-4a81-a525-7d081ac056c5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/30bfe0ac-6511-43e2-917c-ea1151465574/web/2_1736775319242.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.60 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0088502513181</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2206625871</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Foxglove Flowers, Lifelike Silk Artificial Flowers with Long Stem</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiColour WHITEMaterial SilkProduct dimensions 10D x 25W x 95H centimetersSpecific uses for product Home DecorAbout this item🌸 Foxglove Flowers: Bring the beauty of nature indoors with these lifelike silk artificial foxglove flowers, perfect for any decor style. 🌷 Silk Flowers: Made from high-quality silk, these artificial foxglove flowers have a lifelike appearance and a soft touch. 💐 Fake Flowers: Enjoy the charm of flowers without the maintenance; these fake foxglove flowers offer long-lasting beauty. 🌿 Flowers for Decoration: Create stunning floral arrangements with these artificial foxglove flowers, adding a touch of sophistication to any room. 🏡 Artificial Flowers: Elevate your space with these elegant and realistic artificial foxglove flowers, ideal for home, office, or event decoration. 🌺 Artificial Flowers for Decoration: Perfect for adding a pop of color to your decor, these artificial foxglove flowers enhance the aesthetic appeal of any space. 🌿 Flowers for Decoration: Create stunning floral arrangements with these artificial foxglove flowers, adding a touch of sophistication to any room. 🏡 Home Decor Aesthetic: Enhance your home decor aesthetic with these elegant and realistic fake foxglove flowers, suitable for any room or style.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/05b2e571-0291-4812-849c-eb0c43b346a8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/01f8fb00-a0e6-4ff5-b0ec-dbab561e343e/web/2_1736774816107.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022066258713</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6447981313</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Protea Flower, Real Touch Silk Protea for Flower Arrangements, Faux Protea Artificial Flower with Long Stem, Exquisite  Durable Fake Flower for Valentine Day Wedding (1, red)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type ProteaColour redMaterial SilkProduct dimensions 6D x 22W x 65H centimetersAbout this itemReal Touch Elegance: Experience the beauty of real touch with these artificial protea flowers, adding a touch of elegance to your space. Versatile Usage: Ideal for various applications, including creating romantic flower arrangements, Valentine's Day bouquets, and home crafts, these faux protea flowers are versatile. Long Stem Design: With long stems, these artificial flowers offer flexibility in creating stunning arrangements, making them perfect for Valentine's Day surprises. Exquisite and Durable: Crafted with precision, these faux protea flowers boast exquisite detailing and durability for long-lasting enjoyment, making them a meaningful Valentine's Day gift. Romantic Wedding Ready: Perfect for wedding decorations and creating a romantic atmosphere, these artificial protea flowers are Valentine's Day ready. Home Decor Accent: Enhance your home decor with these realistic silk protea flowers, creating a romantic and welcoming atmosphere for Valentine's Day. Tabletop Elegance: Elevate your table decorations with these faux flowers, making them a romantic centerpiece that captivates attention for a Valentine's Day celebration. Easy Valentine's Day Decoration: Whether for creating a romantic ambiance at home or surprising a loved one, these artificial flowers make Valentine's Day decorating hassle-free. Report an issue with this product</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/bd4f2f60-9f9c-4a20-b05a-4abf23af67d7</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1ca9e965-25a2-4785-a73d-dd4e0b8872c9/web/3_1736774727096.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.80 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064479813134</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4056185441</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Leaves with Arrangement and Vase | Real Look Fake Leaves for Home Office Restaurant Decorations | Beautiful Natural Look Flowers</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial PlasticProduct dimensions 8D x 12W x 35H centimetersSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemHigh Quality Material: High quality silk and eco-friendly soft touch material, natural and realistic, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: You can definitely use this artificial, Peony Flowers in a range of permanent floral arrangements. In a mixed flower design with roses, peonies, and greens, make it the focal point. For a 'white wedding' themed affair, add it to your white centerpieces, or gather a few stems to create a Peony wedding bouquet for the bride. We also love all-hydrangea arrangementsFlowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/534f7f11-178b-4cd4-bf6c-fc6a0e9c8d44</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/78659245-3ff2-4a68-8bd5-9bf9a1c121cd/web/1_1736775882154.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0040561854414</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8167324443</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Flowers with Arrangement and Vase</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour greenMaterial PlasticProduct dimensions 5D x 7W x 15H centimetersAbout this itemHigh Quality Material: High quality silk and eco-friendly soft touch material, natural and realistic, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: You can definitely use this artificial, Peony Flowers in a range of permanent floral arrangements. In a mixed flower design with roses, peonies, and greens, make it the focal point. For a 'white wedding' themed affair, add it to your white centerpieces, or gather a few stems to create a Peony wedding bouquet for the bride. We also love all-hydrangea arrangementsFlowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cc77d56a-0576-4a48-ab60-f410787ca09a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b5faab64-5bec-4c8b-98da-f2a5fdd7db72/web/1_1736775921437.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>24.75 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0081673244434</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4987649881</g:id>
      <g:title>Smeg 50's Retro Style Aesthetic 2 Slice Toaster 950 W 1035 W TSF01RGAU Rose Gold</g:title>
      <g:description>A elegantly deep drawn sheet steel two slice toaster featuring a retro design and extra wide slots for nice thick slices of bread and bagelsThe flashy illuminated dials offer up to six varying browning levels to get the toast at the ideal texture for the most delicious results; also includes a bagel functionIncludes handy defrost and reheat functions so you can easily toast your bread or bagels straight from frozeRemovable touch-release stainless steel crumb tray makes quick and easy work of disposing all of those excess crumbsBuilt-in cord storage keeps your kitchen countertops nice and tidy, while the anti-slip feet keeps everything stable and in placeOverviewEnjoy your breakfast in style with this elegantly designed two slice toaster The quality drawn sheet steel construction is complimented by a retro design that really adds elegance to your kitchen countertop This toaster features two extra wide slots that are big enough for nice thick slices of bread and bagels with a bagel function to give you the best results The flashy illuminated dials provide up to six different browning levels to get your toast at the ideal texture for delicious results It's all about functionality with this toaster, featuring defrost and reheat functions, you can quickly toast straight from frozen in a matter of minutes The removable touch-release stainless steel crumb tray makes it really easy to dispose of the excess crumbs This two slice toaster also includes built-in cord storage to keep your kitchen countertops neat and tidy, while the anti-slip feet keeps it stable and comfortably in placeSpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation CountertopColour Name Rose GoldEnergy Used ElectricToaster Wattage 901 To 1300 WattsProduct Length 19. 5 CmProduct Height 19. 8 CmProduct Width/Depth 32. 5 CmWattage 1035 WModel Number TSF01RGAUModel Name TSF01RGUK</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/069c027f-7e6f-4ee3-aed9-818efa03fce6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0f64b42a-4721-40bd-841e-03c7a1668b42/web/1_1736844620512.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049876498818</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6770753015</g:id>
      <g:title>Dyson Purifier Cool Formaldehyd Tp09 Purifying Fan (Nickel/Gold)</g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemDual Functionality: HEPA Air Purifier Bladeless Fan in one which projects smooth purified air per second. Backward airflow (Diffused) mode purifies without coolingTechnical DetailsBrand DysonColor Nickel/GoldPackage Dimensions 110 x 26. 4 x 25. 8 cm; 8. 58 kgItem Weight 8. 58 Kilograms</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3c057952-9310-4e69-839f-e6d7f1ee4e68</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b3d4616c-9ab7-4246-91e8-f6338f2a84e6/web/1_1736845382478.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price> AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0067707530155</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1848334462</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Microwave Oven with 5 Power Levels - Easy Reheating, Fast Defrost Cooking </g:title>
      <g:description>Geepas 20L Microwave Oven Geepas Microwave Oven has as an appealing look with 700W of microwave power to provide quick and convenient cooking in your home. For added functionality, there's also an essential defrost setting, saving you time so that you can cook meals straight from the freezer. And can handle all of your cooking, reheating, and defrosting requirements. With a compact &amp;amp; stylish design, this 20-liter capacity suitable for a standard dinner plate is ideal for cooking a variety of meals in minutes. With 5 selectable power levels, you can tailor your cooking experience and equip with a timer for added convenience. The painted stainless steel interior eliminates rusting and provides even heat distribution; What's more, the timer with cooking end signal for accuracy and precision and comes with a removable and dishwasher safe glass turn-table for easy cleaning. Prepare Varieties of dishes to choose from either Pizza, Chicken, Meat, Vegetables, Fish, Pasta, Soup or Porridge, Steamed Salmon, Potatoes and Asparagus. Reheat - With five microwave power levels to choose from, you can ensure all your food is cooked or re-heated to the optimum temperature. Auto-Defrost - This microwave has defrost setting, all you have to do is input the food and select the ideal defrost timeSpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name WhiteEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Wattage 1000 - 1299 WProduct Height 24 cmProduct Width/Depth 33 cmCapacity 20 LWattage 1100 WFeatures Adjustable Temperature, Alarm, CordedModel Number GMO1899-20LSModel Name GMO1899</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e7d09301-c44b-46c6-9aeb-534fddc36066</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/21a81d38-a0a2-4247-93f0-89377d2c698f/web/1_1736846953465.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>155 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0018483344627</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9572519273</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Air Fryer 4 L Pot| Non-Stick Coating with Vortex Frying Technology| Multiple Function</g:title>
      <g:description>LARGE CAPACITY: A 4. 0-liter air fryer with a nonstick coating that is perfect for making a family mealMULTIPLE FEATURES: Equipped with Vortex air frying, it is suitable for oil-free cooking and making fries, bread, cake, meat, chicken, steak, etc. VORTEX TECHNOLOGY: The air fryer employs VORTEX air frying technology, which cooks food 30% faster while using 99% less oil, resulting in delicious, non-greasy results. OTHER FUNCTIONS: It has an adjustable temperature from 80 to up to 200 degrees Celsius and a 1–60 minute timer. RATINGS: AC 220-240V 50Hz 1500 WOverviewCrispy cravings, guilt-free! The Geepas air fryer allows you to prepare healthy and delicious food without oil. This air fryer is made of premium-quality materials and is designed and manufactured to make everyday cooking easier. The 4. 0-liter air fryer ranks high in looks and efficiency. It is ideal for preparing perfectly fried, healthy, low-fat food without oil for the entire family. The air fryer uses VORTEX air frying technology, which cooks 30% faster with 99% less oil and ensures food is not greasy. It helps you prepare delicious foods that are crispy on the outside and tender on the inside with little to no added oil. In addition, it has an adjustable temperature of up to 200 degrees Celsius. You can cook various food items in it, including fries, chicken, sausages, cake, bread, cake, and more. The air fryer is highly durable and corrosion-resistant, and it can serve you well for many years. The basket is made entirely from the finest quality material, is gentle on food, does not flake off, and is hygienic and safe to use. It does not get greasy, so you can get your fried food out easily. The strong and sturdy construction provides effortless cooking. The air fryer is also easy to clean and maintain. The simple design, black and silver color, and utility features make it an ideal option for your kitchen, and it is also an excellent choice for gifting. The Geepas air fryer comes with a 2-year warranty. SpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name BlackEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 3 - 4. 9 LAppliance Wattage 1500 - 1999 WDishwasher Safe NoAdjustable Temperature NoCapacity 4 LWattage 1500 WModel Number GAF37513Model Name Air Fryer</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f4c15fff-7b35-4777-9fdb-7b44524f4e89</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/324dbc7d-df6e-4426-8895-3cd98af7d56f/web/1_1736847224712.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>98 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095725192734</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4319485345</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS Stick And Handheld Vacuum Cleaner, HEPA Filter, 0.9L Dust Bag Capacity, 600W Powerful Motor</g:title>
      <g:description>ALL FLOOR TYPES - The Geepas 600W handheld vacuum cleaner is suitable for all floor types as it has an adjustable floor head that you press down if you want to switch between hard floors (wooden) to soft floors (carpet. ) To do this it is a simple button- this makes it very efficient and easy to use. LONG RANGE &amp;amp; LIGHTWEIGHT - The Geepas 600W is super lightweight which makes it extremely easy to carry from one room to another. You do not have to strain your back by picking this cleaner up. EASY CLEANING - The Geepas 600W is the definition of "easy cleaning" as it will come equipped with the tool, dusting bag, and hand-held stick. This means you can not only do your hard and soft floors with the cleaner but also your skirting boards and anywhere you can think of up to your ceiling. HEPA FILTER - Using modern technology to separate the dust from the air, it is then filtered by the integrated HEPA filter to catch up to 99. 97% of the particles ensuring that only filtered air is expelled back into the room. This is particularly useful for allergy sufferers who suffer when high levels of dust and other particles get expelled back into the air. HIGHLY EFFICIENT MOTOR - To make your cleaning tasks easy, Geepas Vacuum Cleaner is equipped with a powerful 600W motor that delivers strong suction power and ensures long-time operation. The strong force of the vacuum cleaner catches and traps dust from the surface within seconds. This Vacuum Cleaner comes with Transparent dust cup for easy check and we can empty dust cup without hand contacting. OverviewThe Geepas Stick and Hand-Held Vacuum Cleaner is an essential addition to your home cleaning arsenal. This 0. 9-liter cleaner is powerful and compact. This agile cleaner is as efficient as it is mobile, making it ideal for use all around the home and office! With its stylish and versatile design, it makes cleaning effortless, gliding across many floor types such as carpets, hard floors, tiles, marble, and granite with ease. Being lightweight, you can easily carry it from room to room or upstairs and downstairs, making it the perfect vacuum for quick and easy cleaning. Powered by its powerful 600W motor, you can be sure it will get the job done with ease. The size of this vacuum cleaner measures 1100 x 287 x 186 mm. With the long-reach cleaning wand, you can tackle hard-to-reach areas above the floor, and the detachable handheld with a compact tool lets you get into all the smaller areas that would otherwise be unreachable with a full-sized, corded vacuum. SpecificationsInstallation PortableColour Name WhiteEnergy Used ElectricVacuum Dust Capacity Upto 0. 9 LFloor Type Wet &amp;amp; DrySurface Type All FloorsProduct Length 118 cmProduct Height 24 cmCapacity 0. 9 LWattage 600 WCord Length 3. 2 mFeatures HEPA Filtration, CordedModel Number GVC2596NModel Name GVC2596N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b02b1f03-97ac-4af3-a98b-b90f6ed50827</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a5b8932b-df15-4992-b003-54050047781c/web/1_1736848075773.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>129 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043194853458</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9097681642</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Digital Infrared Cooker With 2000W Ceramic Heating Element, 4 Digit LED Display</g:title>
      <g:description>Rating 220 – 240vTouch sensor control infrared cooker4 digital led displayRated power 2000w ceramic heating element8 power/temperature levels for adjustment and 3 hours programmable timerHigh/low voltage protection Multiple function and lock settingAny material suitable for frying pan for example ceramic pot, stainless steel, aluminium, iron, glass pot Automatically turn off after 120 minutes to prevent forget shutdownThis induction cooker displays time on a 4-digit LED screenInduction cooker displays time on a 4-digit LED screen. It allows quick setting and can be easily operated with the touch controls located on top. Makes cooking professional, precise and fastProgrammable stove has a timer function that can be present for cooking meals. Precision in controls allows maximum control over the heat and texture of food. Its design is simple, and it is easy to cleanOverviewThis cooker offers various temperature (60°- 240°) and power (200W – 2000W) levels and helps you create all of your kitchen cuisines with the perfect favour and softness. This product allows quick setting and can be easily operated with the touch controls located on top to serve you the best results needed and to make sure whatever you need cooked is done with perfect ease. This programmable stove also has a timer function that can be present for cooking meals with a precision in controls that ensures maximum control over the heat and texture of food. SpecificationsMaterial PlasticInstallation CountertopProduct Weight 2. 69 KGColour Name Black/White/RedWhat's In The Box Countertop BurnersEnergy Used ElectricProduct Length 36 cmProduct Height 6. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 28 cmWattage 2000 WFeatures Digital, Adjustable Temperature, Travel, Mechanical, PersonalModel Number GIC33013Model Name Infrared Cooker</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8204fa21-f7a0-4c0e-809e-635aa861961e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1484563c-e663-402a-9127-f2c4f08d6e15/web/1_1736847653304.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>104 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0090976816422</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7569374153</g:id>
      <g:title>Automatic Dry Iron | Iron Box with Temperature Settings Dial and Auto Shut Off Function|</g:title>
      <g:description>Thermostatic pilot lamp indicator offers operational safety Non-stick golden Teflon soleplate for smooth and non-stick ironing results Heal rest makes storing during and after use Cord wrap facility reduces clutter AC: 220-240V 50/60Hz 1000-1200W Temperature settings dial gives perfect ironing results all over the fabric Interchangeable cord Protection against overheating Specifications: Brand: Geepas Model Number: GDI23011 Color: White Base Plate Type: Teflon Iron Type: Dry Iron. Provides a big fabric guide on the body which makes it easier to set temperature-sure glide Thermostatic pilot lamp indicator offers operational safety and prevents accidental hazards Temperature setting dial gives perfect ironing results in no less time Cord wrap facility reduces clutter Heal rest makes storing during and after useSpecificationsMaterial PlasticInstallation HandheldColour Name White/Silver/GoldWhat's In The Box Dry IronsEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Wattage 1001 to 1500 WProduct Length 30 cmProduct Height 12 cmProduct Width/Depth 27. 4 cmCapacity 2. 5 kgWattage 1200 WFeatures Corded, Auto Shut Off, Mechanical, Personal, TravelModel Number GDI23011Model Name GDI23011</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/d910b824-6252-47a2-9736-1affe5371803</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3bf015a6-657e-456a-98e9-5c460eae80f1/web/1_1736848881020.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>47 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0075693741530</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2889028113</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 200L Gross/130L Net Capacity, Direct Cool Double Door Defrost Refrigerator With Grip Handle</g:title>
      <g:description>Experience long-lasting freshness. Featuring a large capacity of 200 liters, Geepas offers you a premium-looking double-door direct-cool refrigerator, perfect for families. The refrigerator has a design where the fridge is located at the bottom and the freezer is located at the top. This refrigerator is made from the finest quality materials and has a premium dark silver finish. It is strong, sturdy, efficient, and built to last. The refrigerator can easily fit in your home, apartment, room, dining area, or kitchen and keeps your food and drinks fresh, cool, and healthy. It cools the contents evenly and keeps them fresh for a long time. The double-door refrigerator is equipped with quick cooling technology, so you need not worry about the contents inside. The refrigerator has a freezer area and can store frozen food items such as meat, ice cream, fish, etc. , and there is a fridge area at the bottom where you can store fruits, vegetables, cooked food, water, milk, etc. The bottom fridge area is equipped with unbreakable tempered glass shelves, transparent door baskets, and extra spaces large enough to hold your food and other edibles. These shelves will keep your things sorted and organized. Additionally, transparent organizers help you see if you are running low on any item. The newly engineered refrigerator keeps your food cold, chilled, and fresh for a long time. It uses a low-voltage and low-noise design and works efficiently, thus saving you electricity and money. The externally gripped handle makes it easy and comfortable to open and close. The adjustable front wheel makes it convenient to move the refrigerator. The refrigerator is also easy to clean and maintain. The product measures 553x474x1280 mm in size and comes with a 1-year warranty. 'SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation Floor StandingColour Name SilverWhat's In The Box RefrigeratorEnergy Used ElectricDoor Style Double DoorProduct Height 128 cmRefrigerator Gross Capacity 200 LRefrigerator Net Capacity 130 LProduct Width 55. 3 cmProduct Depth 47. 4 cmFeatures Indicator Lights, Corded, Self Cleaning, Multi-Function, ManualModel Number GRF2209SXEModel Name GRF2209SXE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/0a427b8e-5dec-42cd-a17f-839676f9b692</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/1175faa9-0e46-4a07-8315-544af73833e2/web/1_1736850668828.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>589 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028890281132</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3292939109</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS Electric Turkish Coffee Maker 0.8L Capacity, Stainless Steel | 360-Degree Rotation</g:title>
      <g:description>Geepas presents a perfect coffee warmer that is not only multipurpose but stylish too Constructed from strong stainless steel that is wonderfully stylish, this durable coffee warmer has been designed to last long The beautiful design makes it ultra-stylish and energy-saving coffee pot; it is designed to make a perfect cup of Greek/Turkish/Arabian Coffee and made in a neat &amp;amp; refined style, so it will perfectly fit any design of the kitchen Excellent for preparation of Turkish coffee, foaming milk and more; and prevents overheating And it has a special pouring spout for no-drip pouring, which makes cooking easy, clean &amp;amp; tidy To make things easier, this coffee pot is lightweight too and features heat-resistant strong handle for ultimate comfort &amp;amp; safety with every use, does not transfer heat and features a hole on the end for easy storageAbout UsWith a history of over 3 decades of business behind it, GEEPAS has become a household name in the field of Electronics. Currently available in 82 countries across the globe, our extensive range of deliverables of over 1500 products caters to 360 degree requirements of a household. GEEPAS stands as the world’s largest Electronics brand portfolio and the only company which covers multiple segments like Entertainment Products, Home Appliances, Kitchen Appliances, Personal Gadgets and Lighting Products. What was started in a humble way has evolved into a huge enterprise with over 3000 employees working in over 10 countries today. Our R&amp;amp;D division complies with every international norm and procedure in quality standards while producing top class products that could be called a judicious combination of Quality and Cost. We are duty bound tuned towards introducing products that are consistent in quality, technology, innovation and that provides our customers, value for their investment. Today we strive not to satisfy our customers but to exceed their expectations through a solid after sales service backup, undoubtedly the best in the world. GEEPAS is a constantly evolving brand experience and its success could be attributed to the long term vision of its promoters, the trained professionals that are the helm of affairs. SpecificationsMaterial MetalInstallation CountertopColour Name Silver/BlackWhat's In The Box Warranty Card &amp;amp; User ManualEnergy Used ElectricPower Source ElectricNumber of Cups 1 CupProduct Length 16. 5 cmProduct Height 14. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 12. 5 cmCapacity 8 LWattage 800 WFeatures Personal, Corded, Multi-Function, Spill Resistant, BusinessModel Number GK38050Model Name GK38050</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/79709441-8c86-4272-a4d8-17822b478dec</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/77320a51-a64b-4df0-baa6-57e73aefa294/web/1_1736851565142.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>35 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0032929391099</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2042337983</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Succulent Wooden Potted Plant Mini Artificial Plants with Stone and Grass in Pots, Green Faux Potted Plants for Office Window Table Bathroom Greenery Room Home Decor</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiMaterial Wood, PlasticRecommended uses for product coffeeSpecific uses for product Home DecorIndoor/outdoor use IndoorAbout this itemSize: Height 12cm, wide 9cm and Diameter:12cmMaterial: Plants are made of Eco-friendly soft plastic which has natural fresh color, poisonless and harmless 100% safe. Pots are made real Rustic wood with metal handleFeatures: These adorable potted are perfect to add color to any arrangement. Generous and elegant, well made and vibrant colorUses: Plant Pots Perfect to display on your bookshelf, living room mantle, coffee table, dining room table, cabinet, desk, kitchen, window ledge, foyer and any other place to bring more lifelike colors and organic style. This little cute artificial potted plant can bring a nearly natural view to your home or office. Artificial plant would never wither or nor fade which remains just as fresh-looking and beautiful year after year. doesn't require any maintenance.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e6a42415-ceeb-432b-9992-4b349dc271d6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/90ea2725-d7f6-4e19-bb19-6a9a157b9e27/web/1_1736849724732.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020423379835</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6328686611</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Flowers with Arrangements and Vase | Real Look Beautiful Royal Look Flowers for Home Office Party Decorations | Artificial Flowers with Arrangements (Arrangement38)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type hydrangeaMaterial Arrangement38Product dimensions 12D x 17W x 35H centimetersSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemMaterial: Silk, Wired Stem for flexible arrangementsHigh Quality Material: High quality silk and eco-friendly soft touch material, natural and realistic, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: You can definitely use this artificial, Peony Flowers in a range of permanent floral arrangements. In a mixed flower design with roses, peonies, and greens, make it the focal point. For a 'white wedding' themed affair, add it to your white centerpieces, or gather a few stems to create a Peony wedding bouquet for the bride. We also love all-hydrangea arrangementsFlowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquet. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c23d04c6-97d7-4bab-b1d6-c09f198a03ac</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/dc0d1415-8c74-42c3-b183-31db7d457b89/web/1_1736849614851.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0063286866111</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7939689788</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Pack Of 4 Artificial Carnation Flowers, Lifelike Silk Flowers Bouquet, Realistic Fake Flowers Arrangement, Maintenance-Free  Long-Lasting Faux Flowers Home Office  Wedding Decoration, Red</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type CarnationColour PurpleMaterial Silk, PlasticProduct dimensions 20D x 20W x 32H centimetersAbout this itemDimensions: Total Height - 32m, Flowers Branch Length – 20cm, Diameter - 23cm. (Without Vase)🌸 Realistic Silk Carnations – These lifelike artificial carnation flowers replicate the beauty of real blooms, perfect for enhancing your home or office decor with maintenance-free elegance. 🌿 Maintenance-Free Beauty – Enjoy long-lasting freshness without the need for watering or upkeep. These faux flowers stay vibrant and beautiful, offering a hassle-free decorative solution for any space. 🎨 Vibrant &amp;amp; Lifelike Colors – Crafted with high-quality silk, these faux carnations feature rich, realistic hues that bring a fresh, natural touch to any room, whether displayed in a vase or as a table centerpiece. 💐 Long-Lasting &amp;amp; Durable – Made from premium silk, these artificial flowers are designed for long-lasting durability, ensuring they maintain their vibrant look year-round, whether indoors or outdoors. 💐 Perfect for Weddings &amp;amp; Events – Ideal for wedding decorations, anniversaries, and special events, this artificial carnation bouquet adds timeless beauty to table arrangements, backdrops, and gift displays. 🏡 Versatile Home &amp;amp; Office Decor – These artificial flowers are perfect for living rooms, bedrooms, or offices, adding a touch of floral charm to your interior without the need for constant care. 🎁 Thoughtful Gift Option – Ideal as a gift for Mother's Day, Valentine's Day, or housewarming parties, this carnation bouquet is a thoughtful, maintenance-free present that brings lasting joy to any recipient.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b5a266d9-a18e-4cf5-8f5d-b2f02d042ffe</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/28783c91-8a02-4d18-92d3-2d10b968194b/web/3_1736850902121.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.92 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079396897884</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8524903927</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Portable Powerful 2 Slice Grill Maker with Non-Stick Coated Plates With Safety Locks</g:title>
      <g:description>Make delicious grilled food at home with the Geepas stainless steel grill maker. This grill maker is designed with sturdy and durable materials and is the right choice for your home. The grill maker comes with 2 grill plates with a 2 slice capacity and a non-stick coating to make your favorite grill or sandwich. The plate is non-stick and requires only a very small amount of butter or oil to make your snack delicious and healthy. The grill maker helps you get lovely grill lines on your sandwich and can be used for sandwiches as well as non-sandwich recipes. For instance, you can grill vegetables, chicken, meat, etc. The lid opens up easily, allowing for easy assembly and removal of the contents, making them convenient for daily use. The safety locks on the plates keep the contents secure. Quickly grill your favorite sandwich, be it grilled cheese, garlic bread, or garlic bread, with this easy-to-use knob on the grill maker. You can tell the status of your snack by the power-on and ready-light indicators, thereby avoiding burning your fingers and food. The grill maker is made of durable material and has a cool-touch housing and handle for protection against burns. The non-stick plate is easy to clean and is resistant to corrosion. The sturdy anti-skid feet help to keep the grill maker in place, ensuring maximum safety. You just keep the food in and the temperature automatically adjusts, and once it is cooked completely, the appliance automatically shuts down for your safety. The product is compact and can be stored vertically upright to save space in your kitchen. The black design on the outside makes it an elegant product. The product uses only 750W of power, which means it consumes less electricity and delivers maximum efficiency. This stainless steel grill maker is a great asset to your home and also a thoughtful option for gifting. The product measures 25. 7x10. 8x25. 3 cm and weighs 1. 313 kg. The Geepas grill maker comes with a 2-year warrantySpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation CountertopColour Name Black/GreyWhat's In The Box ToasterEnergy Used ElectricNumber of Slices 2 SlicesProduct Length 22. 4 cmProduct Height 9. 5 cmProduct Width/Depth 22. 3 cmWattage 750 WFeatures Corded, Multi-Function, Spill Resistant, Business, PersonalModel Number GGM6001Model Name GGM6001</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/fafdbf6d-7e4f-43ab-8456-f1d9488d932e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bf80781e-47d7-4e4a-b449-149fd3cdf922/web/3_1736850910961.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>49 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0085249039271</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2226995464</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2 Pcs LED Tea Lights Candles Battery Operated Romantic Realistic Flickering Flameless LED Candles With Malted Edge Design Votive Candles for Home Tealight Dinner Wedding Party Décor (Large)</g:title>
      <g:description>Finish type PolishedBase material PlasticProduct dimensions 5D x 5W x 12H centimetersItem weight 1 KilogramsLamp type Light Emitting DiodeAbout this itemSize: Height – 12cm, Diameter – 5cm. (Package Include 2 Pcs)High-Quality Material: YATAI’s candles are crafted to perfection with the finest quality materials so you can enjoy unique results. The candles are made with plastic and operated by 3 x LR1130 batteries that are replicable. Safe &amp;amp; Environment Friendly: 100% SAFE! Enjoy all the benefits of traditional candles and none of the negatives! We care about your safety, and a risk of fire shouldn't be a concern. No more dripping-hot wax, no more smoke or worry about falling asleep without blowing out the candles. Are You Planning A Party OR Wedding? You will love these battery-operated flameless candles. . . Just set them into your favorite lantern, chandelier, sconce or candle holder or mix with other decorations. Moving Wick &amp;amp; Dancing Flame: Flameless taper candles feature realistic looking flameless candles on the market. Light glows and dances on the moving flame piece providing a stunning, real looking effect. No more "static" wicks on your flameless taper candles. This real looking flame taper candles can be used as a great gift as well as a wonderful set for your own home decor and also for restaurant, office, weddings, dinner, parties, children rooms decoration.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/95c5ae71-363e-463d-a79d-7b9087609991</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/60f7468f-fccc-4ed4-8cd1-6d08cbd63a50/web/1_1736850626992.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.29 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022269954641</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4824869758</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 7/Heads Silk Peony Flowers Artificial plants For Anniversary Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type PeonyMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion Wedding, AnniversaryAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Peony FlowersColor: Purple/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5c9ef078-c919-4b12-8233-b40dc0a5c2f8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c9ea019d-44da-49a2-835c-37c0bd506fe4/web/1_1736850714086.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.65 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0048248697583</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6896639099</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Hand Blender - Stainless Steel Blades with 2 Speed for Baby Food</g:title>
      <g:description>1. GEEPAS 400W 3-IN-1 HAND BLENDER - Hey, I am your Helping Hand to Create Perfect Smoothies! INJECTION SHELL AND MULTIFUNCTIONAL The hand blender blade is covered with a white injection shell. It prevents the contents from flying off while blending. This hand blender can handle all types of blending, juicing, and meat grinding. It comes with an 860ml large capacity bowl suitable for most of your blending work. 2. DETACHABLE STAINLESS STEEL STICK, COMFORTABLE GRIP - The stick is made of sturdy stainless steel. It can be removed easily. It makes cleaning really easy. You can keep it tidy without having to put in much effort. The handle is designed to fit perfectly in your palm. This allows the best anti-slip grip and comfortable holding for non-stop blending. The size of this blender is 18. 5x13. 2x21. 8cm. 3. 400W TWO SPEEDS AND DC MOTOR - This hand blender comes with two variable speeds. You can use the one which fits your grinding requirements. It uses a fast-working powerful DC motor. Allows free rotation and excellent results in blending. SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation HandheldColour Name Red/Silver/ClearWhat's In The Box 860 ml Chopper Bowl, Egg Whisk, Hand BlenderEnergy Used ElectricProduct Length 13 cmProduct Height 18 cmProduct Width/Depth 30 cmCapacity 860 mlWattage 400 WFeatures Corded, Mechanical, Personal, Travel, ProgrammableModel Number GHB6136Model Name GHB6136</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9f13dbd4-c2d6-4822-9fae-98a9e543952e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/d60541d4-0712-4f6b-bda5-a7e06e264474/web/1_1736849717945.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>68.50 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068966390993</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3597954226</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Rechargeable Mini Water Dispenser Portable and Light-Weight Pump with Easy Press Mechanism</g:title>
      <g:description>A high quality rechargeable mini water dispenser with a USB charge plug and play feature for easy water dispensingThe dispenser has one button operation and two simple steps of installationThe dispenser has an LED night light mode to assist you in finding it in the darkThe unit is compatible with all bottle types and is a perfect match for bottled mineral and purified water cansOverviewEnjoy effortless dispensing of water with the Geepas rechargeable mini water dispenser. Made from the finest quality material, the dispenser is a convenient and portable solution for all your hydration needs and is sure to last a lifetime. The dispenser is non-toxic and hygienic and provides a healthy and safe way to enjoy your glass of water. The dispenser is specially designed to provide smooth and easy dispensing, allowing you to save time and energy when lifting heavy water gallons or containers. The pump features a USB plug and play, and you can easily dispense the water from anywhere at any time. The one-button operation makes it simple to use, and the LED nightlight mode helps you easily find the dispenser in the dark. The rechargeable feature makes it portable and can be used anywhere without a power outlet or changing batteries. The dispenser is compatible with bottled mineral water and purified water, making it a unit for all bottle types. The 65 mm-diameter handheld unit is small and easy to carry, making it ideal for indoor and outdoor use. The dispenser provides you with the easiest access to clean and refreshing drinking water. Featuring quality material, a simple white design, and easy one-button operation, this rechargeable mini water dispenser is a smart companion for staying hydrated throughout the day at your office, home, or even while traveling. The dispenser includes a 2-year manufacturer's warrantySpecificationsMaterial 100% PlasticColour Name White and BlackEnergy Used BatteryProduct Length 13 cmProduct Height 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 13 cmWattage 4 WModel Number GWD17034</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/438191a0-c229-4ff7-be7e-4b67ccae92bc</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0ec1ebb5-333d-4cb7-a66f-4fbe31c481f0/web/2_1736850009940.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.30 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035979542268</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9553999757</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Electric Kettle, Plastic Water Kettle, Boil Dry Protection</g:title>
      <g:description>Geepas electric kettle is made of healthy and hygiene stainless steel inner with delicate polish. With a 1. 7L water capacity it can provide about 6 to 8 cups of water for your whole day drinking. Double wall structure: This electric water kettle is constructed with double walls which not only prevents your hands from being scaled while touching but also keeps water warm much longer. Glass Finish Layer: The Exterior plastic glassy finish layer is for heat insulation and offers stylish looking. Power: This powerful 2200W kettle boils water within 2 5 minutes, 5mins to boil a full pot (1. 7L). It boils the water in very little time as it will stop heating after reaching the boiling point and saves energy. Safe with Auto Shutoff: If you accidentally let the kettle run without water, the protection turns it off automatically. You do not have to worry about safety when the kettle is running. Our stainless steel kettle with a wide mouth for easy cleaning and filling. Stay cool ergonomic handle:The cord can be stored in the power base when not use. It has a rotational base comfortable for both right and left handed persons for easy use. 360 degrees rotatable and is comfortable both right as well as left handed people. Lid is place perfectly in a place and is locked by safety lock to avoid spills and keep your kitchen clean. To keep the kitchen tidy, the base has integrated cord storage so it can be tidied away at your convenience &amp;amp; the handy 360° base means it can be comfortably used by right &amp;amp; left-handed people. This Electric kettle is a great appliance for creating that rejuvenating and re-energizing feel. Made using premium quality materials, it ensures long-lasting use. Additionally, it is uniquely designed to provide comfortable usage. SpecificationsMaterial PlasticInstallation CountertopProduct Weight 870 gColour Name Black/ClearWhat's In The Box GEEPAS Electric Kettle 1. 7 L 2200 W GK38027 BlackEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 1. 1 To 2. 5 LAppliance Wattage Above 1960 WattPower Source ElectricNumber of Cups 5 Cups &amp;amp; AboveProduct Length 21 cmProduct Height 23. 8 cmProduct Width/Depth 15. 8 cmCapacity 1. 7 LWattage 2200 WFeatures Indicator Lights, Personal, Travel, Business, Adjustable TemperatureModel Number GK38027Model Name GK38027</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9325895f-aca8-41b9-a177-9f97f30d9177</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/bb150c17-9f8c-4fdb-9d36-c3cdb3bb2268/web/2_1736850434131.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>35 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0095539997570</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6671573041</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Vacuum Cleaner With Powerful Suction, Low Noise Design, Dust Full Indicator</g:title>
      <g:description>This Vacuum Cleaner has a smart feature that shows an indication when the dust bag in full so that you can empty it. The engine is the most vulnerable and expensive part of the vacuum cleaner. Therefore, the power and quality of detail are very important. The copper motor of this handheld hoover with a power of 1400 watts is able to cope with large volumes of work. Thanks to the high-quality material, the vacuum cleaners can last for a long time. All you need to do to prevent engine damage is to avoid overheating the blind cleaners. This vacuum cleaner has a powerful suction will collect all tough dust and keeps your house clean and tidy. This Geepas vacuum cleaner has a high capacity collection bag and holds the dust even after using the cleaner multiple times. The long, electrical cord and the vacuum in reaching an impressive cleaning radius of the 3. 2-meter cable. Easily clean every corner of your home. Plastic Insert Tube, Plastic Floor Brush with full Geepas Vacuum Cleaner. Allows you to move freely with a vacuum cleaner throughout the house and not be afraid that there will not be enough cord length. Due to the automatic cord re-winder function, the storage becomes easy and space-saving. No need to buy additional filters or dust bags. A capacious container is built into the that collects all the dust and dirt with the easy clip-on system, powering on/off and emptying the vacuum cleaner is clean and hassle-free. After filling it, you just need to rinse it with water. If you're looking for a quiet vacuum cleaner that still provides strong performance, this one is ideal for you. It has a multi-cyclone. SpecificationsMaterial ABSInstallation PortableColour Name Blue/BlackWhat's In The Box 1x Plastic Insert Tube, 1x Plastic Floor Brush, 1x Geepas Vacuum CleanerEnergy Used ElectricVacuum Bag Type BaggedVacuum Dust Capacity 1. 5 to 1. 9 LFloor Type Wet &amp;amp; DrySurface Type All FloorsProduct Length 34 cmProduct Height 21 cmCapacity 1. 5 LWattage 1400 WCord Length 3. 2 mProduct Width 25 cmFeatures Corded, Manual, Portable, Programmable, Removable BowlModel Number GVC2595Model Name GVC2595</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3782e26e-f2a3-4870-99b1-e239ac98bec6</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/671f0eb9-ba51-4aa6-8dc6-84b47fd76dba/web/1_1736851298979.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>91.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066715730410</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1299707979</g:id>
      <g:title>Air Fryer Equipped With Vortex Air Frying Technology| 7 L Capacity With A Rack</g:title>
      <g:description>The Geepas Air Fryer is a revolutionary kitchen appliance that combines the benefits of healthy cooking with delicious results. With its large 7-liter capacity, you can prepare family-sized meals with ease, making it perfect for gatherings and dinner parties. The 1800W power output ensures rapid heating, reducing cooking time while maintaining even heat distribution. The air fryer features innovative VORTEX technology, which circulates hot air to cook food evenly, producing a crispy, golden-brown exterior, and a tender interior. The adjustable time and temperature controls allow for a range of cooking options, from baking and roasting to frying with minimal oil. The non-stick coated pan and tray are easy to clean, and the full stainless steel housing adds durability and style to your kitchen. This air fryer cooks food up to 30% faster and uses 99% less oil, making it a healthier choice for your favorite fried foods. Whether you\'re making crispy fries, juicy chicken, or even desserts, the Geepas Air Fryer delivers delicious results every time. Plus, it\'s backed by a 2-year warranty, ensuring long-lasting performance and reliability. Experience guilt-free cooking with the Geepas Air Fryer’s oil-free cooking technology. Using little to no oil, this appliance offers a healthier alternative to traditional frying methods, allowing you to enjoy your favorite fried foods without compromising on taste. Perfect for health-conscious individuals and families The Geepas Air Fryer is engineered to cook food up to 30% faster than conventional methods. It uses 99% less oil, producing delicious and crispy dishes that are not greasy, making it a perfect choice for those looking to reduce fat intake without sacrificing flavor. Prepare your favorite snacks, such as fries and nuggets, with up to 80% less fat compared to deep frying. The air fryer uses a unique cooking method that removes excess fat while retaining the food’s natural flavor and texture. The adjustable time and temperature settings allow for precise control over your cooking. You can set the temperature between 100°C and 200°C, making it suitable for baking, roasting, and frying a variety of dishes Pan with Tray, Both with Non-Stick Coating: The air fryer features a non-stick coated pan and tray, ensuring that your food does not stick and is easy to remove. The coating also simplifies the cleaning process, maintaining the appliance’s durability and longevity Full Stainless Steel Housing: The sleek stainless steel housing not only adds a modern touch to your kitchen but also ensures durability and resistance to wear and tear. The high-quality material protects the air fryer from damage and makes it easy to clean. Timer and Temperature Range The timer can be set from 1 to 30 minutes, and the temperature is adjustable from 100°C to 200°C, offering versatile cooking options. This flexibility allows you to cook a wide range of dishes, from crispy fries to tender roasts. SpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name SilverWhat's In The Box User manual, Warranty cardEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 5 L &amp;amp; AboveAppliance Wattage 1500 - 1999 WDishwasher Safe NoAdjustable Temperature NoProduct Length 46 cmProduct Height 40 cmProduct Width/Depth 40 cmCapacity 7 LWattage 1800 WFeatures Adjustable Temperature, Corded, Indicator Lights, Multi-Function, WashableModel Number GAF37506Model Name GAF37506</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/3cb77645-3fba-45ac-bc70-a1a23a1281ff</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/5b6eb2bc-8434-4529-b64a-08279426d6cc/web/1_1736856900113.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>145 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012997079792</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7901196139</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Home Decoration Artificial Plants Potted Simulation Flowers Decorated Flower - Artificial Plant</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiSpecific uses for product Home DecorPackage information PotNumber of Items 1Item weight 1. 1 PoundsAbout this itemHome Decor Category: Artificial PlantsBrand: YataiName: Succulent Plant</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7490e607-487a-43f3-b2a7-76d16e8ee012</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2713e29a-698d-4c96-bd40-b75352ee8837/web/1_1736850467250.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25.20 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0079011961396</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6813669859</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas 6 KG Fully Automatic Washing Machine| Top Load Equipped with Big Pulsator</g:title>
      <g:description>Automatic fault correction with digital time/LED displayWater level selection and low noise optionTransparent lid with pump and soaking water optionAutomatic imbalance correction and Adjustable footInner tub is made of stainless steelOverviewThis Washing Machine, designed to revolutionise your laundry experience. With its efficient and user-friendly design, this washing machine offers hassle-free operation and outstanding cleaning performance. Our fully-automatic Washing Machine caters to all your laundry needs, from delicate fabrics to heavily soiled clothes. Its powerful motor ensures thorough cleaning while conserving energy, making it a sustainable choice for your household. This versatile appliance can be used for a variety of purposes, including washing clothes, bed linens, towels, and more. Whether you're a busy parent, a working professional, or a college student, this washing machine simplifies your laundry routine, giving you more time to focus on what matters most. SpecificationsInstallation FreestandingColour Name White/BlackEnergy Used ElectricWashing Machine Operation Type Fully AutomaticLoad Style Top LoadProduct Height 93 cmModel Number GFWM6800LCQ</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/c14417ba-0f37-47b3-b993-a661dd89ec78</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/904bbe7e-e313-48e8-9de0-d5eb3666815b/web/1_1736853058014.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>540 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068136698591</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5221933720</g:id>
      <g:title>Geeps 60 Cm Cooking Range, 4 Gas Euro Pool Type Burners  3mm Flat Burner Caps</g:title>
      <g:description>The Geepas 60*60 Cm Cooking Range is designed to elevate your cooking experience with a range of features that prioritize efficiency, safety, and convenience. This kitchen appliance is a versatile addition to your culinary toolkit. Spacious Cooking Area: With a generous 60*60 cm cooking area, this range provides ample space for preparing various dishes simultaneously. Whether you're whipping up a family feast or tackling multiple courses, the cooking area allows for efficient meal preparation. Gas Burners: The range is equipped with four gas Euro pool type burners, each featuring 3mm flat burner caps. These burners are designed for high efficiency, ensuring that your cookware is heated evenly and food is cooked to perfection. The burners offer the flexibility required for a wide range of cooking techniques. Control and Stylish Design: Silver color double knobs and an aluminum handle not only enhance the range's aesthetics but also make it user-friendly. The double knobs allow separate control of the oven and burners, granting you the precision needed for customized cooking. Oven Features: The multifunctional oven offers a range of cooking options. The convection single oven lets you bake, roast, and prepare a variety of dishes. The inclusion of a grill and rotisserie function adds to its versatility, allowing you to achieve diverse culinary creations. Safety and Convenience: The range is designed with safety and convenience in mind. The system glass top lid serves both as a protective cover for the burners when not in use and as an elegant design element. Push button ignition simplifies the process of lighting the burners, ensuring quick and hassle-free operation. A notable safety feature is the full safety auto gas cut off, which provides peace of mind by automatically shutting off the gas supply in case of emergencies or unexpected situations. Efficient Cooking: The range is equipped with wide enamel pan support, which ensures stability for your cookware, even when using larger pots and pans. This feature provides a secure cooking surface, reducing the risk of accidents. Enhanced Insulation: The double layer brown glass wool insulation of the oven contributes to efficient and even cooking. It retains heat, helping dishes cook uniformly and maintain their desired textures and flavors. Stainless Steel Top Panel: The top panel is constructed from durable stainless steel, which not only adds to the range's longevity but also makes it easy to clean and maintain. This top panel can withstand the rigors of daily cooking and cleaning, ensuring that your range maintains its quality and appearance. In summary, the Geepas 60*60 Cm Cooking Range offers a blend of efficient and versatile cooking features, safety mechanisms, and stylish design elements. Its spacious cooking area, gas burners, multifunctional oven, and user-friendly controls make it a valuable addition to any kitchen. Whether you're preparing simple weeknight dinners or hosting elaborate gatherings, this cooking range provides the tools you need for culinary success. SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation FreestandingColour Name Silver/blackWhat's In The Box 60*60 Cooking Range, Warranty Card, User Manual,Baking Tray, Rotisserie Grill, Ignition connection cable with plugNumber of Burners 4Type Of Burner GasType Of Oven GasProduct Height 81 cmModel Number GCR6057Model Name GCR6057Number of Burners 4. 0</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4bb0768b-5483-4db0-b7ff-efb22c5486c0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/85c5c780-5c4b-46d4-aa36-3200f82366b3/web/2_1736851134221.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>749 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052219337200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1048164732</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Home Decor, L-Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour Light GreenMaterial Silk, PlasticProduct dimensions 48D x 48W x 48H centimetersAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 🌼 Table Centerpiece: Arrange these artificial eucalyptus leaves in a vase or create a stunning table centerpiece for weddings, parties, or everyday decor. 🎄 Christmas Decorations: Incorporate these eucalyptus leaves into your Christmas flower decorations, adding a festive and natural touch to your holiday celebrations. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 🌿 Durable &amp;amp; Low Maintenance: Unlike real plants, these fake eucalyptus leaves require no watering or maintenance, ensuring lasting beauty without the hassle. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/65401e0e-dc8a-4056-8837-2ee7ef4b479b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/fe4950a7-2a03-4e02-ad4c-04356e82d912/web/1_1736851781299.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010481647328</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3559617605</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Plants and Plastic Flowers artificial flowers for decoration flower silk flowers artificial decoration can make bouquet flowers flower wedding wreath decoration (Purple)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type BambooColour PurpleMaterial Silk, PlasticRecommended uses for product Living spaces, bedrooms, dining rooms, garden areas, patiosAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Ericaceae PlantColor: GreenMaterial: Glue silk, real touch, bamboo stick and flower spongeSize: D-25cm, H-37cmFeatures: This tiny arrangement simple design makes it a clutter-free way to bring life to small living spaces or the perfect desk accessory. Uses: It is ideal to decorate your living room with its elegance. You can decorate your living space, bedroom, dining room, garden area, patio with this lovely plants.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/abb4e301-43bc-4cde-878c-7d0525f3e59f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/888a2b58-5416-491e-8472-9748d4cc666c/web/1_1736851629215.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.01 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0035596176051</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9614613955</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Artificial Silk Hydrangea Flower Bunch Arrangements Large Fake Floral Bundles Home Wedding Bouquet Table Centerpieces Party Decoration -RED (1)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour OtherMaterial OtherRecommended uses for product Home Decor, Event Decor, Office Decor, Indoor Decor, Outdoor DecorAbout this itemSize: Bouquet Diameter- 50cm Height-30cm (Not Include decorations)Material: YATAI Hydrangea Flowers are made of silk, full and soft petals, Natural-looking. Wire wrapped with plastics is used for firmness and angle-adjustable in creating the stems. The beauty of fake hydrangea flowers bouquets is that you can enjoy the look you crave, but don't have to worry about have no time watering, pruning, and other maintenanceRealistic artificial hydrangea flower is suitable for outdoor or indoor decoration, decorating your garden and party, hanging on the wall or doors, placing it on the table and so onUV protected faux flower bouquet made of high-quality plastic and fabric material, bendable, non-toxic and durable for long time use, a brilliant alternative to live planting</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/860aba54-0dbf-49fc-919b-0e701d478bc1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/3f17a87f-ffab-4b3d-a96b-fa1e827f5eb3/web/1_1736851390608.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.01 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0096146139551</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3303803255</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Home Office Decor, Pine-Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour Pine GreenMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product Office DecorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves. 💐 Realistic Appearance: The faux eucalyptus leaves closely resemble their natural counterparts, providing a realistic and long-lasting alternative to fresh flowers. 🎄 Christmas Decorations: Incorporate these eucalyptus leaves into your Christmas flower decorations, adding a festive and natural touch to your holiday celebrations. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/8972a3d4-9824-4e2a-8935-41259406bc8d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/12e2ff5c-61bc-4c67-8e39-972162d8415b/web/1_1736852473793.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033038032552</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4451025870</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Greenery Stems Eucalyptus Leaf Silk Greenery Bushes Plastic Plants Floral Greenery Stems for Home Party Wedding Decoration (2)</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cmHigh Quality Material: Soft touch, Glue Silk, plastic stems, iron wire is wrapped in the stem, easy to adjust the effect you want. Features: Flowers are well-made and vibrantly colored. They will add extra vitality to your home, also add extra color and texture to your bouquetUses: A great decoration for dinner table, wedding, party, birthday, shower, meeting room décor, and anywhere that you want to put. They are perfect for making bouquets, centerpieces, cake flowers or any other flower decorations/arrangements that you want at your wedding, party, baby shower or home.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/53edf236-35d7-4cbc-8570-8b86f0e0f619</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8863dca5-3b11-4c5c-aef7-2973d198478e/web/1_1736852639372.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044510258704</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4355171104</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS Digital Air Fryer Equipped With Vortx Air Frying Technology| Oil Free Cooking Digital Display</g:title>
      <g:description>Reduce oil and enjoy the crunch and softness of deep-frying without using as much. You can make tasty, healthy cuisine without using any oil when you use the Geepas digital air fryer. Designed and produced to simplify daily cooking, this air fryer is composed of high-quality materials. The 5. 0-liter digital air fryer ranks high in looks and efficiency. It is ideal for preparing perfectly fried, healthy, low-fat food without oil for the entire family. The air fryer uses VORTEX air frying technology, which cooks 30% faster with 99% less oil and ensures food is not greasy. It helps you prepare delicious foods that are crispy on the outside and tender on the inside with little to no added oil. The fryer has a digital display with a touch screen. In addition, it has an adjustable temperature of up to 200 degrees Celsius. You can cook various food items in it with its 10 preset programs, including fries, chicken, sausages, cake, bread, cake, and more. The air fryer is highly durable and corrosion-resistant, and it can serve you well for many years. The basket is made entirely from the finest quality material, is gentle on food, does not flake off, and is hygienic and safe to use. It does not get greasy, so you can get your fried food out easily. The strong and sturdy construction provides effortless cooking. The air fryer is also easy to clean and maintain. The simple design, black color, and utility features make it an ideal option for your kitchen, and it is also an excellent choice for gifting. The Geepas digital air fryer comes with a 2-year warranty. SpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name BlackEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 5 L &amp;amp; AboveAppliance Wattage 1500 - 1999 WDishwasher Safe NoAdjustable Temperature NoProduct Length 39 cmProduct Height 36 cmProduct Width/Depth 31. 5 cmCapacity 5 LWattage 1600 WModel Number GAF37527Model Name GAF37527</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4cdd9074-e972-4818-9754-0bfc4bd6bd8b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/2bcbfc90-c908-47a8-acad-964c24db1554/web/1_1736852801013.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>175 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0043551711049</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4245350853</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Fairy Lights Battery Operated 17Ft/5M With 50 LED String Lights Twinkle Festival Lights Indoor LED Lights For Bedroom Garden Wedding Party Festival Holiday Tree Decorations</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour Warm WhiteBrand YataiIndoor/outdoor use IndoorSpecial features Energy EfficientLight source type LEDPower source Battery PoweredLight colour Warm WhiteTheme FantasyOccasion Christmas, Wedding, HalloweenStyle ContemporaryAbout this item17ft With 50LEDs: 17ft/5m long ultra-thin fairy string with 50 super bright LEDs, 4 inches distance between every LED bulb, 12 inches clear protective cable between the battery case and the first LED. Quick ON/OFF Button: These fairy lights powered by 3AA batteries (not included). Durable PVC made small battery case comes with a ON/OFF switch, easy to turn it on and off. Wide Application: The LED fairy lights are great decorations for patio, indoor/outdoor, garden, home, camping, Christmas, Halloween holiday party, bedroom, bar, kitchen. The charming soft lighting can create excellent illumination and a warming and romantic atmosphere at night. Easy To Shape &amp;amp; Mold: These string lights can be easily shaped any symbols you like. such as love/star shape, logo signs, furniture, Xmas tree, bottles/can. Its great surprise for you and your family, friends, lovers etc. Energy Efficient: NO heat problem, no flicker. The ultra slim thin copper wire decreases energy cost.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5ebedb9d-7855-4132-b225-93523ed27571</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/66a1ef0a-ba65-43c6-805a-9339f01dad9c/web/1_1736859023309.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0042453508535</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9178119132</g:id>
      <g:title>Air Fryer 1.8 L With Vortx Air Frying Technology| Oil Free Cooking,</g:title>
      <g:description>In an age of fast paced, busy and stressful life, a home cooked meal with the right balance of flavor and health is often left to be desired. Delicious food is finally guilt free, thanks to this Air fryer. It cuts down on the oil so that you can relish the mouthwatering, crispy food without the added fat. Allows for a wide range of cooking experience. SpecificationsMaterial PlasticInstallation FreestandingColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box Air FryerEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity Upto 1. 9 LAppliance Wattage Upto 1499 WDishwasher Safe NoAdjustable Temperature NoProduct Length 38. 7 cmProduct Height 34 cmProduct Width/Depth 38. 7 cmCapacity 1. 8 LWattage 1100 WFeatures Dishwasher Safe, Auto Shut Off, Mechanical, Personal, TravelModel Number GAF37516Model Name GAF37516</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e187b367-6279-4843-b117-15149ec49a2b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/c20434b3-cab9-4356-bb82-96df5cf7b0ea/web/2_1736858544989.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>94 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0091781191322</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6010900307</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Wedding Decor, Red</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product Office DecorIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 💐 Realistic Appearance: The faux eucalyptus leaves closely resemble their natural counterparts, providing a realistic and long-lasting alternative to fresh flowers. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 🌿 Durable &amp;amp; Low Maintenance: Unlike real plants, these fake eucalyptus leaves require no watering or maintenance, ensuring lasting beauty without the hassle. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7f5a72a0-08ec-4c3b-9cd0-0e4a499750eb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/69b32da2-bfec-48c1-be89-7db7cb79031d/web/1_1736853775868.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0060109003074</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1584151540</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Microwaves Oven 20L, Re-Heating and Fast Defrosting </g:title>
      <g:description>With this Geepas microwave, be your own chef! Reheat, defrost and prepare all kinds of meals with this 20-liter Geepas microwave. You will have the freedom to check if your food is cooked properly with a pull handle. Heat and defrost any food you want anytime. Moreover, the 35-minute timer will ensure you get the right crisp, heat and flavors oozing from your food, without sweating it out!HighlightsThe Geepas 20 Liter Microwave Oven GMO1894 is convenient to use. It is made from good-quality material to make it durable and long lasting. It has a marvelous capacity of 20 liters and features 6 microwave levels. Model no. : GMO1894Color: WhiteType: Microwave OvenPower supply: 220-240V 50/60HzPower consumption: 1200 Watt SpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name WhiteWhat's In The Box 1 x Otg OvenEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Wattage 1000 - 1299 WProduct Length 25 cmProduct Height 20 cmProduct Width/Depth 15 cmCapacity 20 LWattage 1200 WModel Number GMO1894-20LNModel Name GMO1894-20LNItem Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/86576104-11d3-4df5-b8ef-2efa7cda95e1</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b371c458-8b0d-41ed-867b-c64e84fb1c70/web/2_1736853270018.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>165 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015841515408</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5596237630</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Plants 2 Bunch Daisy Flowers For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type daisyColour multiIndoor/outdoor use IndoorOccasion Anniversary, BirthdayAbout this itemBrand: Yatai;Name: Daisy Flowers;Color: Cream/Green/Pink;Material: Artificial;Size: Height-32cm;Features: The beautiful and colorful combination captures the attention of your guests;Uses: An ideal arrangement for indoor decoration, a girlfriend or boyfriend, anniversary, birthday or Grandparent's Day, It's a repeat favorite of customers</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/316a17a9-7c5a-4f4c-89dd-91a0d7da1a07</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/8ddf93e7-f50a-4ee0-a169-e3baa29b08ae/web/1_1736857703836.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055962376304</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4462098533</g:id>
      <g:title>Mixer Grinder 750W Powerful Copper Motor with Stainless Steel Jars and Blades Unbreakable</g:title>
      <g:description>Check out this mixer grinder if you want a reliable one right now. An all-in-one design combined with a high level of performance makes a mixer grinder an all around solution for grinding chutneys, spices, or smoothies. Mix and grind your ingredients to perfection with the Geepas 3-in-1 mixer grinder. The mixer comes with three jars stainless steel jar, a dry grinding steel jar, and a chutney jar. Featuring a modern design with a durable body, this set includes a stainless steel jar set, stainless steel razor-sharp blades, and unbreakable jar caps. The jars and blades are made of premium-quality stainless steel materials, which are resistant to corrosion, 100% quality guaranteed, and food-safe. The powerful 750-watt copper motor simplifies working in the kitchen and provides a hassle-free cooking experience. The jars are equipped with lids to keep the contents intact and in place, so that nothing will fall off or spill. These high-efficiency blades made from stainless steel can cut through difficult ingredients easily and mix and grind them to the proper consistency, and they are robust enough to provide the most effective results. It is used to prepare batters, masalas, chutneys, shakes, purees, and so on. The jars are made of durable, food-grade stainless steel with leak-proof lidsSpecificationsMaterial ABSColour Name Silver, redEnergy Used ElectricWattage 750 WModel Number GSB5081NModel Name GSB5081N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2bd926a1-ed7b-430e-96d6-e91aa1575631</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/701853fb-24f8-4d12-94d0-9868bcfbe068/web/1_1736857506913.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>162.55 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0044620985330</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6412501873</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Stainless Steel Grill Maker, Power and Ready Light | Non-Stick Cooking Plate</g:title>
      <g:description>"You can make healthy and delicious grilled foods with your family for a fun dinner. Embrace the little pleasures with the Geepas stainless steel grill maker. This grill maker is designed with sturdy and durable materials and is the right choice for your home. The grill maker comes with grill plates with a non-stick coating to make your favorite snack. The plate is non-stick and requires only a very small amount of butter or oil to make your snack delicious and healthy. The grill maker helps you get lovely grill lines on your sandwich and can be used for sandwiches as well as non-sandwich recipes. For instance, you can grill vegetables, chicken, meat, etc. The lid opens up to 180, allowing for easy assembly and removal of the contents, making them convenient for daily use. Quickly grill your favorite sandwich, be it grilled cheese, garlic bread, or garlic bread, with this easy-to-use knob on the grill maker. You can tell the status of your snack by the power-on and ready-light indicators, thereby avoiding burning your fingers and food. The grill maker is made of durable material and has a cool-touch housing for protection against burns. The non-stick plate is easy to clean and is resistant to corrosion. The sturdy anti-skid feet help to keep the grill maker in place, ensuring maximum safety. You just keep the food in and the temperature automatically adjusts, and once it is cooked completely, the appliance automatically shuts down for your safety. The product is compact and can be stored vertically upright to save space in your kitchen. The black and silver design on the outside makes it an elegant product. The product uses only 1600W of power, which means it consumes less electricity and delivers maximum efficiency. This stainless steel grill maker is a great asset to your home and also a thoughtful option for gifting. The product measures 32. 3x11. 5x29. 6 cm and weighs 2. 34 kg. The Geepas grill maker comes with a 2-year warranty. "SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation CountertopColour Name Silver/BlackWhat's In The Box GEEPAS Grill Maker 1000 W, manualEnergy Used ElectricProduct Length 11. 6 cmProduct Height 29. 6 cmProduct Width/Depth 33 cmCapacity 0. 1 kgWattage 1600 WFeatures Portable, Corded, Manual, Indicator Lights, PersonalModel Number GGM5394Model Name GGM5394N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5aa81f79-fd84-41e4-beb5-e687e3fc33c3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/652c1d2b-4acd-40e4-8da2-42b88a8f67c7/web/2_1736856170076.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>89 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0064125018739</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6613626581</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 12pcs Dragonfly On A Stick Dragon Fly Garden Stakes Dragonflies Garden Ornaments Patio Decoration Miniature Fairy Garden Decoration (12, Yellow)</g:title>
      <g:description>Colour YellowBrand YataiTheme FairyMaterial PolypropyleneStyle GardenAbout this itemmade of good PP material with exquisite workmanship for durability. Great simulation dragonflies for outdoor yard decorations, lawn ornaments, planter decorative supplies. With spring connection, so it will be the real dragonfly, more and vivid. A variety of color combinations, which is beautiful, a gift option for dragonfly lovers. Suitable for garden, backyard, lawn, courtyard,, sidewalk and other place. Our Service: If You Don't Like Or Whatever, please feel free to contact us, We'll Instantly Full-Refund or Offer Replacement Service for free.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/72e106ed-e517-4aa2-be8e-ed6d14bcb75f</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/191f4acc-b2fa-4915-9dc9-18c315613a96/web/1_1736859140252.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0066136265812</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1608808801</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Wall Hanging Handmade Bamboo Fiber Wooden Flower Round Basket with Metal Chain Home Garden Indoor Outdoor Decoration (Small)</g:title>
      <g:description>Size: SMaterial WoodColour OtherSpecial features LightweightStyle TraditionalShape RoundAbout this itemBeautifully display plants and flowers with a traditional style plant basket. With a traditional look, this plant hanging basket set highlights your favorite plants and flowers with simplistic beauty. Each basket features a circular frame, coconut husk fiber liner, hanging chains, and a secure S-hook for hanging. Home and garden lovers will enjoy quick and easy planting with a few easy steps. Both lovely and low maintenance, this garden essential is sure to accent your patio, lawn, or garden. Use multiple baskets and plants hung at different levels to create your own unique decorative effect. An eco-friendly Bamboo Fiber and a hanging chain are included for ease in displaying your gorgeous plants and flowers.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/f851bf4e-49fa-4810-87e4-9a2f764baf87</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0a3b49ce-8337-44cf-8a45-f6045c34135d/web/1_1736858877179.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.10 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0016088088014</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5489328878</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Home Decor, Maroon</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour MaroonMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product Office DecorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves. 🌼 Table Centerpiece: Arrange these artificial eucalyptus leaves in a vase or create a stunning table centerpiece for weddings, parties, or everyday decor. 🌿 Durable &amp;amp; Low Maintenance: Unlike real plants, these fake eucalyptus leaves require no watering or maintenance, ensuring lasting beauty without the hassle. 🎄 Christmas Decorations: Incorporate these eucalyptus leaves into your Christmas flower decorations, adding a festive and natural touch to your holiday celebrations. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/5b8d59d0-4b3d-4a36-94b8-4988373d6b53</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0a9c4fd8-e607-4fe3-be30-f46ffcd845cd/web/1_1736852180165.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0054893288786</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>9813033139</g:id>
      <g:title>Automatic Rice Cooker 3 in 1 Functions Non-Stick Inner Pot Automatic</g:title>
      <g:description>Prepare healthy and tasty food with the Geepas automatic rice cooker. This rice cooker is made of premium-quality materials and is designed for your everyday cooking. The rice cooker ranks high in both looks and efficiency. It has a capacity of 0. 6L and is ideal for preparing meals for the entire family. The rice cooker has a 3-in-1 feature which allows you to cook, steam, and keep your food warm. An indicator light on the outside helps you monitor warm and cook operations. The rice cooker is highly durable, corrosion resistant and can serve you well for many years. The inner pot is made of non-stick material that does not flake off and is hygienic and safe to use. It also has an extra thermostat. The newly designed rice cooker features an automatic shut off and an overheat protection feature. This ensures that the food does not get burned and provides you with an effortless cooking experience. The rice cooker is also easy to clean and maintain. The product comes with a premium-quality tempered glass lid that allows you to monitor the food inside, ensuring better heat retention during the process and retaining the freshness and flavors of the food. A heat-resistant material makes the handles on the pot and lid easy to handle. The package also contains a measuring cup and spoon. The rice cooker weighs 1. 5 kg and is 22. 5 X 22. 5 X 25 cm in dimension. The Geepas automatic rice cooker comes with a 2-year warranty. SpecificationsInstallation CountertopColour Name WhiteEnergy Used ElectricProduct Length 22. 5 cmProduct Height 26. 1 cmProduct Width/Depth 22. 5 cmCapacity 0. 6 LWattage 300 WModel Number GRC4324NModel Name GRC4324N</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/ea0b7d7e-b438-4dc5-a1c4-8c9115341576</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/02e3defc-a8ac-4eab-a4a3-0434925e1f5e/web/1_1736856384199.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>59 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0098130331392</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>4985086493</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Office Decor, Pink</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour PinkMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product Office DecorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 💐 Realistic Appearance: The faux eucalyptus leaves closely resemble their natural counterparts, providing a realistic and long-lasting alternative to fresh flowers. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 🌼 Table Centerpiece: Arrange these artificial eucalyptus leaves in a vase or create a stunning table centerpiece for weddings, parties, or everyday decor. 🍃 Versatile Decor: Ideal for wedding decorations, table centerpieces, and office decor, these artificial eucalyptus leaves offer endless possibilities for styling. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e601d0dd-1ba0-4ac9-8536-98ae37230feb</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4f957c87-e774-4765-a9d0-d5c3469dfeb6/web/4_1736853637647.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0049850864936</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5238288837</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 7/Heads Luxury Silk Daisy Flowers Artificial Plants For Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type DaisyMaterial fabricSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion WeddingAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Daisy FlowersColor: Peach/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2f01d153-577b-4e84-90db-0a3bcba96838</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/4689bde8-3ec6-401f-83f1-215e59672580/web/1_1736855971717.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0052382888370</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5003350447</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Eucalyptus Leaves Flower, Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus Garland Faux Flowers, Green Leaves Eucalyptus Plants, Realistic Fake Flower Arrangement, Artificial Leaves Bunches for Home Decor, P-Green</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusColour Pink GreenMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product Home Decor, Office DecorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Premium Quality: Crafted from high-quality materials, these faux eucalyptus leaves ensure durability and beauty, enhancing any space with their timeless elegance. 🌿 Lifelike Silk Eucalyptus: Enjoy the beauty of lifelike silk eucalyptus garlands, bringing a touch of nature indoors with realistic green leaves. 🌸 Faux Flower Arrangement: Create stunning flower arrangements with these eucalyptus leaves, adding a natural and elegant touch to your home or office decor. 💐 Realistic Appearance: The faux eucalyptus leaves closely resemble their natural counterparts, providing a realistic and long-lasting alternative to fresh flowers. 🌿 Durable &amp;amp; Low Maintenance: Unlike real plants, these fake eucalyptus leaves require no watering or maintenance, ensuring lasting beauty without the hassle. 🏡 Home &amp;amp; Office Decor: Elevate your interior decor with these artificial leaves bunches, perfect for adding a refreshing and vibrant atmosphere to any space.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/6ea068d5-0cef-4616-a025-ce6350b5a0c8</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/be6b1e4b-b776-413d-b144-ec195576ee55/web/1_1736853307171.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.01 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0050033504471</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3385337748</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Gross  205L Net Capacity Double Door Defrost Refrigerator| With faster Cooling</g:title>
      <g:description>The 240L Gross - 171L Net Capacity Double Door Defrost Refrigerator is a dependable and feature-rich appliance designed to enhance your food storage and preservation experience. With its spacious design, advanced cooling technology, and convenient features, it is an excellent addition to any kitchen. One of the key advantages of this refrigerator is its substantial capacity. With a gross capacity of 240 liters and a net capacity of 171 liters, it offers ample space for storing a wide variety of fresh and frozen foods. Whether you're a family stocking up on groceries or an individual with diverse food storage needs, this refrigerator has the capacity to accommodate your items. The refrigerator's faster cooling system is engineered to chill your groceries and beverages rapidly. This quick cooling not only ensures that your food items maintain their freshness but also helps in preserving their nutritional value. It's a valuable feature for those who want their beverages to be refreshingly cold and their fruits and vegetables to stay crisp. Long-lasting freshness is a priority in this refrigerator's design. It is built to keep your food items fresher for extended periods. This is particularly beneficial when it comes to preserving the flavor, texture, and quality of your groceries. Whether it's fruits and vegetables or dairy products, you can trust this refrigerator to maintain their freshness. In addition to its generous storage space, this refrigerator offers extra features for convenient and efficient organization. It includes tempered glass shelves that are both strong and adjustable, allowing you to organize your items with ease. The glass shelves are also easy to clean, making maintenance a hassle-free process. To ensure the safety and security of your stored food, this refrigerator comes equipped with a handle lock and key. This feature allows you to restrict access to the refrigerator, preventing unauthorized openings and ensuring the integrity of your groceries. Temperature control is an essential feature that allows you to customize the cooling settings according to your specific needs. Whether you want to chill beverages at a colder temperature or maintain a milder climate for your fruits and vegetables, this refrigerator provides flexibility. The refrigerator is illuminated with energy-efficient LED lighting. LED lights not only provide better visibility within the fridge but also consume less energy, contributing to lower electricity bills and reduced environmental impact. In summary, the 240L Gross - 171L Net Capacity Double Door Defrost Refrigerator is a well-rounded cooling solution for your kitchen. With its spacious design, faster cooling, long-lasting freshness, convenient organization, and security features, it ensures that your food remains in optimal condition. This refrigerator combines practicality with efficiency, making it a valuable addition to any home. SpecificationsMaterial MetalInstallation Floor StandingColour Name SilverEnergy Used ElectricProduct Height 141 cmCapacity 240 LRefrigerator Gross Capacity 240 LRefrigerator Net Capacity 205 LProduct Width 54 cmProduct Depth 54 cmModel Number GRF2400SXE</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/428fb65c-c7d3-429e-aed6-9362f06eec4e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b63f7028-dcb1-406d-841a-cb29b0144784/web/1_1736858738154.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>699 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0033853377487</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>7093040215</g:id>
      <g:title>Rechargeable LED Flashlight, USB Rechargeable| 8hrs Working Torch</g:title>
      <g:description>This Geepas Rechargeable LED Flashlight has a 1*3W hi-power LED light that gives bright cool white light which is less harsh and gives you a day like light appearance. This torch is very much useful in emergency light in case of power failures at your home. Ensures wireless working with built-in high capacity 3. 7V 3000mAh rechargeable lithium battery, rechargeable for multiple times and ensures safe using. The strong LED light works continuously for 3. 5hours and weak light for 8hours. You can charge this flashlight directly with a USB cable. This torchlight stands out unique for its power beam hyper bright cool white LED and this will let you identify the exact objects even in the darkness. Capable and suitable to resist in any situation and environment with its rigid body to help you out in the darkness. Compact but also comfortable to hold, the torch fits very well in your hand or bag. Whether you\'re camping or taking a late night walk with the dog, the reliable Geepas LED Flashlight is a good companion. Durable and easy to handle, it is an ideal handheld flashlight for use around the house or in an emergency. And can be used for camping, hiking, fishing, running, dog walking, power outages, emergencies, targeted searches and general household use. Take the flashlight when you go camping or picnics on your next adventure. The flashlight weighs 0. 263kg. "" '"SpecificationsProduct Weight 0. 28 KGColour Name BlackWhat's In The Box User Manual , Warranty CardType of Flashlight HandheldControl Method Push ButtonModel Number GFL51052Model Name GFL51052Item Quantity 1</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/1a1eb3a9-e3e9-4074-ba04-33349e92cd44</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b11c3783-84d7-40ab-9404-08d4587a2846/web/1_1736858214432.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>25 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0070930402151</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6888354867</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI 2pcs Artificial Eucalyptus Greenery, Realistic Faux Green Leaves Flowers with Stems for Vase Filling, Long-Lasting  Maintenance-Free Fake Flowers, Faux Flower Bouquet for Home Event Decor</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type EucalyptusMaterial Silk, PlasticSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemSize: Total Height - 48cm, Flowers Length - 38cm. 🌿 Realistic Design: This artificial eucalyptus greenery features lifelike green leaves and stems, perfect for vase filling or standalone displays. 💐 Versatile Decoration: Enhance room decor, table decor, or bedroom decor with these timeless fake flowers. 🌸 Maintenance-Free: Enjoy the charm of fresh flowers without watering or care—these artificial plants stay vibrant all year round. 🌺 Customizable Arrangements: Combine with pampas flowers, dry flowers for decoration, or garlands to craft unique centerpieces. 🎉 Event Ready: Add sophistication to wedding decoration, onam decor, or festive Eid decor with these elegant faux stems. 🏡 Home Elegance: Ideal for decoration items for living room, these flowers artificial for decoration elevate any space with natural beauty. 🎁 Perfect Gift Idea: A thoughtful home decor gift, anniversary gift, or Mother's Day gift for loved ones who adore greenery. 🏢 Office &amp;amp; Event Decor: Ideal for office decor, these lush stems create a professional and welcoming ambiance.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/62d0441e-466d-42f4-bf3c-fed2fef96cf0</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/09f27dda-08e4-4e03-8cf0-ad3436e1c5cd/web/1_1736854058982.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0068883548675</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2288714114</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Bottom Loading Water Dispenser| Normal, Hot and Cold Function, Compressor Cooling</g:title>
      <g:description>The Geepas Hot, Cold, and Normal Water Dispenser is a versatile and efficient solution to meet your daily hydration needs, providing you with the convenience of instantly accessing hot, cold, or room-temperature water. Whether you're at home, in the office, or any other setting, this water dispenser offers a reliable and efficient way to access the water you need. Hot, Cold, and Normal Water Dispenser: This dispenser is designed to accommodate all your water temperature preferences. You can enjoy a soothing cup of hot tea or coffee, a refreshing glass of cold water on a hot day, or simply room-temperature water whenever you desire. The three temperature options cater to a variety of hydration preferences, making it suitable for every member of your household or workplace. Door Cover: The dispenser features a door cover that serves multiple purposes. Firstly, it enhances the aesthetics of the dispenser, giving it a sleek and clean appearance. Secondly, it helps protect the water reservoirs from dust and contaminants, ensuring that the water you dispense is clean and hygienic. High Efficiency Compressor Cooling System: The high-efficiency compressor cooling system ensures that the cold water is chilled quickly and consistently. This not only provides you with refreshing cold water on demand but also does so in an energy-efficient manner, helping you save on electricity costs. Stainless Steel Water Tank: The water dispenser is equipped with a stainless steel water tank for both hot and cold water. Stainless steel is known for its durability, corrosion resistance, and ability to maintain the purity and quality of the water it stores. This ensures that the water you dispense is safe, clean, and free from contaminants. Safety System to Avoid Dry Heating: The dispenser incorporates a safety system to prevent the heating element from dry heating. This safety feature ensures that the heating element operates efficiently and without the risk of overheating or damage. 3 Tap Design: The three-tap design of the dispenser makes it incredibly user-friendly. You can easily select the temperature you desire by using the respective tap—hot, cold, or normal. The intuitive design ensures that everyone can access the water they prefer without any hassle. The Geepas Hot, Cold, and Normal Water Dispenser combines convenience, efficiency, and safety to provide you with a reliable source of hot, cold, and room-temperature water. Its versatile temperature options, durable stainless steel tank, and safety features make it an ideal addition to your home or office. Stay hydrated and enjoy your favorite beverages with ease, courtesy of this dependable water dispenser. SpecificationsInstallation Floor StandingColour Name Grey &amp;amp; BlackEnergy Used ElectricProduct Height 100. 5 cmCapacity 5 LWattage 590 WModel Number GWD17037Model Name GWD17037</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/650dea0a-5cbd-4224-beca-318684538eae</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7cd8244a-cde5-4007-894d-a508bd80d075/web/4_1736857756053.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>479 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0022887141140</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8274051937</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Silk Hydrangea Flowers 7/Heads Artificial Plants For Home Party Bridal Wedding Decoration</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetIndoor/outdoor use IndoorAbout this itemBrand: Yatai;Name: Hydrangea Flowers;Color: Peach;Material: Fabric/Silk;Size: H-45cm, Head-17cm, Diameter per bunch-28cm ;Heads: 1 bunch &amp;amp; 7 heads;Uses: It is an ideal arrangement for home decoration, wedding party bridal bouquet, hotels, restaurants, office, and festival decoration. ;Features: It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look. ;Made from high-quality materials and vibrant colors.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/b69b525d-6d38-4e9c-94d4-337e98914f2a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/b2236561-52c0-468d-a3f6-950f34cfd907/web/1_1736854692518.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0082740519370</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1257228319</g:id>
      <g:title>Stick And Handheld Vacuum Cleaner, HEPA Filter, 1.2L Dust Bag Capacity</g:title>
      <g:description>The Geepas Stick and Hand-Held Vacuum Cleaner is an essential addition to your home cleaning arsenal. This 1. 2-liter cleaner is powerful and compact. This agile cleaner is as efficient as it is mobile, making it ideal for use all around the home and office! With its stylish and versatile design, it makes cleaning effortless, gliding across many floor types such as carpets, hard floors, tiles, marble, and granite with ease. Being lightweight, you can easily carry it from room to room or upstairs and downstairs, making it the perfect vacuum for quick and easy cleaning. Powered by its powerful 600W motor, you can be sure it will get the job done with ease. With the long-reach cleaning wand, you can tackle hard-to-reach areas above the floor, and the detachable handheld with a compact tool lets you get into all the smaller areas that would otherwise be unreachable with a full-sized, corded vacuum. SpecificationsInstallation HandheldColour Name GreyWhat's In The Box Vacuum Cleaner, User Manual and Warranty cardEnergy Used ElectricVacuum Bag Type BaglessVacuum Dust Capacity 1 to 1. 4 LFloor Type Wet &amp;amp; DrySurface Type All FloorsProduct Length 16 cmProduct Height 61 cmCapacity 1. 2 LWattage 600 WNoise Level 85 dBSuction Power 9 kPaProduct Width 15 cmFeatures HEPA FiltrationModel Number GVC19055-GRModel Name GVC19055-GR</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/09649c19-be46-4906-80ec-e2604edbac45</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/14c7a8af-e19e-4a3b-aa48-513e05b4e0c3/web/1_1736853600510.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>95 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0012572283194</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1089800106</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 7/Heads Luxury Silk Daisy Flowers Artificial Plants For Bridal Bouquet Arts/Crafts Project</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type DaisyMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product Home DecorIndoor/outdoor use Outdoor, IndoorAbout this itemHome Decor Category: Artificial Mixed Floral Arrangements;Brand: Yatai;Brand: Yantai;Name: Daisy Flowers;Colour: Purple/Green;Material: Fabric/Silk;Size: H-45cm, Heads-10x9cm, Diameter per bunch-22cm;Heads: 1 bunch 7 heads</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e60281ec-6fbd-4c29-be15-a38362c9fcdd</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f2bea74f-797c-4259-920a-f781defa898c/web/1_1736855899331.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0010898001065</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>6147043558</g:id>
      <g:title>Geepas Electric Tea Kettle 1.8 L, Auto Shut Off And Boil Dry Protection, Safety Lock Lid</g:title>
      <g:description>GEEPAS 1. 8L ELECTRIC KETTLE - Lets Heat Things Up, Quick &amp;amp; Easy. The Geepas Electric Kettle provides you with a stylish design Textured Kettle combining a high stainless material for a rich feel meaning it will bring style to any kitchen worktop. The large, 1. 8-litre capacity means you'll have plenty of hot water for any large family or team or work colleagues. LARGE CAPACITY 1. 8L - A roomy and large kettle is perfect for your whole family. With its help, you can make 8 cups of tea or coffee and treat yourself to a pleasant drink not only of household members but also unplanned guests. This electric kettle with a 1. 8L capacity is big enough and it has clear water level lines on the outside so you can fill it with the exact amount of water you need. ERGONOMIC HANDLE -To make pouring comfortable and easy the electric kettle features an ergonomic handle for easy pouring. PERFECT POUR - The 'perfect pour' water spout helps you to avoid spills &amp;amp; keep your kettle clean without any hassle. SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation CountertopColour Name Silver/BlackEnergy Used ElectricAppliance Capacity 1. 1 To 2. 5 LAppliance Wattage 1500 To 1850 WattCapacity 1. 8 LWattage 1500 WModel Number GK5454BModel Name GK5454B</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/7e53fffa-9fc1-408f-89af-6313a3782fb5</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/ae82dec5-218c-4d17-ab01-d59cb91c3a00/web/4_1736852079177.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0061470435587</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>8073824161</g:id>
      <g:title>GEEPAS 180LGross/ 132L Net Capacity, Double Door Refrigerator - Durable Double Door Refrigerator</g:title>
      <g:description>eep beverages, vegetables, or food fresh with the Geepas Direct Cool Refrigerator. It comes with faster cooling technology to maintain the freshness of your food. It is perfect to save energy and features temperature control and tempered glass shelves. This double door refrigerator delivers rapid cooling performance to maintain the food freshness, chills drinks and make more ice. Built in natural deodorizing filter to eliminate the strong smell, odour from your fridge and holds natural flavour and aroma of the preserved food. This Geepas Freezer consumes less power without any deviation in the performance, so your fridge will stand out from other with Smart and money saving for you than any other. It has User friendly option to control the temperature with adjustable temperature option to set according to your requirements. This crystal white colour refrigerator is stylish integrated and modern look with power cool with less energy consumption. Geepas dual door refrigerator has the rapid cooling performance to chill your drinks in no time and let you enjoy the unplanned meet up with friends. Enjoy fresh and crisper fruits, vegetables, meat, fish, Juices, milk products, and more contents fresh for a long time. This Refrigerator will surprise you with its energy efficiency, keeping all your food contents fresh and maintains the natural flavour. This double door fridge is ideal for family, bachelors, and shopkeepers. It is capable to preserve all the food which you may require for a week and also more. The freezer comes with an adjustable temperature option to set according to your requirements. You will also receive a key to lock to avoid your childrens' and pets from opening the door. This Refrigerator has durable glass shelves designed to offer you comfortable access to the items in your fridge. It is spill-proof as your fridge may have lots of beverages or liquid like milk, juice, etc. SpecificationsMaterial MetalInstallation FreestandingColour Name SilverWhat's In The Box RefrigeratorEnergy Used ElectricInverter Technology InverterProduct Height 126. 6 cmWattage 120 WRefrigerator Gross Capacity 180 LRefrigerator Net Capacity 132 LProduct Width 49. 2 cmProduct Depth 45. 3 cmFeatures Portable, Corded, Travel, Ergonomic, PersonalModel Number GRF1856SPNModel Name GRF1856SPN</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/cf0f6052-0902-4174-8105-fd124d4b9507</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/985a28a7-8a5f-4576-acdc-7ccd94a622af/web/5_1736851823994.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>549 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0080738241616</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2069392720</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai 5 Heads Luxury Silk Hydrangea Flowers Artificial Plants For Multiple Occasions</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type HydrangeaColour PurpleMaterial SilkSpecific uses for product BouquetAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Hydrangea FlowersColor: Pink/Green</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/9e435573-e89b-4e75-948a-ec429cd01c98</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/a20e00ee-cbc5-46ca-b159-2892b5876fbf/web/1_1736855684590.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0020693927200</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5546375878</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Artificial Plants Rose Flowers Bridal Wedding Party Decor Bouquet Real Touch Flower</g:title>
      <g:description>Brand YataiPlant or animal product type RoseColour PurpleSpecific uses for product BouquetOccasion WeddingAbout this itemBrand: YataiName: Rose FlowersMaterial: Real Touch Material</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/87cdfa61-078c-4cdb-a660-b6fde950021e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/e7720139-1b33-4aa1-aa4b-e0fb75af5836/web/1_1736858613937.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>26.09 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055463758784</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
