<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Ayshei</title>
    <link>https://ayshei.com/</link>
    <description>Your one-stop shop for the latest fashion items</description>
    <item>
      <g:id>1501810252</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Patio Lounge Low Height Chair with Arm Rest for Reading Garden Chair Outdoor Reclining</g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions &amp;amp; Weight Capacity: Height - 64cm, Length – 71cm, Width – 57cm. Weight - 3kg. Weight capacity of 120kgMaterial: Durable alloy steel frame will ensure long-lasting value. Made with a Polyester coated material makes it easy to wipe down and clean with a cloth. Wide Application: Ideal for camping, sitting in the garden, barbecue, additional, concerts, sports events, and beaches. Backpackers, car camping, or wherever you travelPortable: This lightweight bag chair for adults is compact. Space-saving design folds small for easy portability. Perfect lawn chair for adult with a carry bag for picnic, or beach. Great chair</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/056efcb2-6d94-49f2-bdc0-d9dac9d0038b</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/88688876-49f4-4781-bd53-4f0eae68aa2d/web/1_1736251227030.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>108 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0015018102523</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3886538592</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Decor Artificial Money Plant 1.7 Meter High Artificial Tree in Plastic Pot for Home Garden </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height – 170cm, Diameter – 75cm, Pot Size: Height – 13cm, Diameter – 15cm. High-Quality Material: Nearly natural PVC plastic branches, and plastic pot. Made it high-quality materials and vibrant colors. Design: YATAI’s plant stays forever green and is an explosion of green. Lush and elegant green leaves. It is designed with a fine detailing to lend it a realistic look and is placed in a lovely pot to accentuate its attractive look. Versatile Use: Bring modern sensation combined with garden charm into your place. This plant will bring in a sense of calmness and peace to your house and will soothe your eyes every time you look at it. Artificial plants are beautiful for any decoration project or home decor. An ideal arrangement for home, office, hotels restaurants decoration, it's a repeat favorite of customers. No Maintenance Required: With our artificial tree, never worry about watering or wilting leaves ever again. Effortless to manage, our artificial plants for decoration are maintenance free and will liven up your home, kitchen or bathroom. Looks full and fresh every day.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/4dbb7164-c067-4b16-90c4-a6f306657d1d</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f0190e09-e55f-4894-a19b-66732a1b9a80/web/1_1736251592521.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>159 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0038865385925</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>3981716114</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Large Collapsible Wagon Cart Heavy Duty Wagon Garden Carts with 8" All Terrain Wheels</g:title>
      <g:description>Large capacity, large internal size 70 x 47 x 89 cm Sturdy frame supports 60 kg / 132 lb;Folding utility vehicles are ideal for transporting shopping, family outingsThe 360-degree beach wheels and the adjustable handle - the folding cart has heavy and thick rubber wheels - rotate 360,Convenient and compact storage - easy to fold and simple storage;Instant installation, no assembly required;It can be folded into a handbag for easy storage. Sturdy and washable -- the folding station wagon is made of 601D waterproof polyester, detachable and easy to clean by hand or hose. The camping beach station wagon frame is made of steel. The sturdy black steel frame of the beach outdoor multifunctional station wagon frame is more stable</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/e8ff0b90-d816-4b05-bd26-981e66edf8c3</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/0196f900-864d-48b1-9186-5b8fc6fe072d/web/1_1736250791608.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>160 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0039817161147</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>5570201085</g:id>
      <g:title>Yatai Decor Wood Chair and Table For your Perfect Home – Metal Folding Dining Table Set For Garden </g:title>
      <g:description>About this itemChair Size: Height - 78cm, Width - 48cm, Length-42cm. Table Size: Height - 71cm, Diameters - 55cm. Table folds down for easy storage. Material: Made of hardy wood and metal, its strong and durable. This 3pc bistro set including one square table and two folding chairs. The suitable size prefers for patio, garden, bistro, balcony or room. The high chair back gives you good support and makes you more relaxed. This set is made with wood and metal frame!it's perfect for placing on your patio. balconies and smaller gardens. Best of all, each piece offers a folded design for convenient storage in the offseason. This bistro set with table and 2 chairs set is ideal for relaxing or entertaining in the sunshine. The small, round table is made from hardwood and folds for easy storage. The 2 folding chairs fit comfortably around the table and can be stowed easily.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/11cde3a9-5a71-4916-a3dd-eb34bbaf679a</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/7aeafb11-88bc-42eb-ac16-4322dd443927/web/1_1736250992028.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>239 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0055702010857</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>1702749148</g:id>
      <g:title>Dyson Purifier Cool Tower Fan TP07BN Black/Nickel</g:title>
      <g:description>With a sealed filter system, the Dyson Pure Cool purifying tower fan brings powerful air circulation while also keeping the room’s atmosphere fresh and free of pollutants and various airborne particles SpecificationsMaterial Stainless SteelInstallation Floor StandingColour Name Black/NickelCountry Of Origin AustraliaEnergy Used ElectricProduct Length 12 CmProduct Height 105 CmProduct Width/Depth 20. 4 CmWattage 1600 WModel Number TP07BNModel Name TP07BN</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/2188dc74-1ac6-47dc-9c9d-1862d4081d85</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/61a68170-ae22-47b0-b9bd-6b1f746498d4/web/1_1736235326343.jpeg&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>1399 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0017027491483</g:gtin>
    </item>
    <item>
      <g:id>2820454232</g:id>
      <g:title>YATAI Solid Acacia Wood Sun Lounger Outdoor - Weather-Resistant Adjustable Recliner Patio Chairs </g:title>
      <g:description>Dimensions: Height - 60 cm, Width - 55 cm, Length- 198 cm, (comfortably seats with cushions. Naturally resists termites, rot, decay &amp;amp; moisture. Strong &amp;amp; Durable: Made of hardy Acacia wood, oil finishing, strong and durable. Cushions made of 100% polyester fabric. Built To Last: Built with weather elements in mind, our sturdy wood construction is made of weather-resistant wood and durable canvas. Timeless Gift: Surprise somebody with this awesome outdoor furniture piece! The outdoor chaise is perfect for enjoying the summer weather. Comfortable: Our sun loungers are ergonomic and made of skin-friendly fabrics. The adjustable backrest allows you to choose from 5 levels of personalized comfort, you can lay down on your stomach to enjoy sunbath. Perfect For Outdoors: This relaxing chair is perfect for patios, decks, lawns, poolside and outdoors for enjoying sunshine, having a rest, chatting with your friends or holding party. Assembly Instructions Included: Packaged with detailed, step-by-step assembly instructions.</g:description>
      <g:link>https://ayshei.com/product/68e48710-eb3f-4ed7-9eaf-242d860aea7e</g:link>
      <g:image_link>https://ayshei.com/_next/image?url=https://storage.ayshei.com/prod/public/drafts/f136e28f-b057-4228-b318-2f3077267dff/web/1_1736252210622.png&amp;w=3840&amp;q=75</g:image_link>
      <g:brand></g:brand>
      <g:price>458 AED</g:price>
      <g:availability>in stock</g:availability>
      <g:gtin>0028204542324</g:gtin>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
